All right, I'm done!
The hall's finished!
So fast!
Is there anything I can help with?
Too bad!
There's no need for you today!
What?
The floor's done!
The desks are done!
Yay!
This...
You call this done?!
He's like a mother-in-law!
So strict!
Just accept your loss quietly!
No! I'm not gonna give up!
Nomura-san, are you done wiping the windows?
Huh?
Oh no, not yet...
Everyone's done already, you know.
S-Sorry...
Nomura-san, you're doing the window? I'll help!
No fair, Komiya!
The girls are in charge of that!
Shut up! You guys help too!
S-Sorry...
For what?
For being slow...
Of course it'll take a long time if you wipe carefully.
The places you wiped are really clean.
Th...anks...
Smells like love!
Sniff, sniff... huh?
I-It's not like that...
There you go again.
Even though you say that,
you'll give him some this year right?
Give him what?
Well, it's February...
Oh. Wait, what?
If you want to tell him your feelings,
I recommend homemade.
If you have leftovers, I want some too.
Sure...
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
Madoka-nii-sama,
that day is finally drawing near this year!
We definitely want to make it meaningful this year.
Valentine's
Trends
and
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
Valentine's
Trends
and
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
Valentine's
Trends
and
Counter
measures
Two years ago
Truffles
Last year
Cake
This year??
We tried truffles last year,
and last year I even baked him a cake from scratch.
What happened?
He accepts it every year, but...
You even made some for me? Thank you.
That doesn't sound good...
What if you tried something that appeals more towards your maturity?
Maybe some Western liquor or something?
I see!
Bonbons, right?
What're you talking about?
Isn't it obvious?
It's February, so...
Ogre Seal
B-Bean-throwing?
Oh, Chihiro-kun.
Yeah, let's do bean-throwing too.
Valentine's?
It's barely February.
Yeah, but Miyako-san and Madoka
were having a strategy meeting.
They're really into it, huh?
Well, it has nothing to do with us.
This year you might get some too, Amahara.
Huh? Why?
The class representative, Sugita.
Aya Sugita
Class
Representative
I heard that last year she gave
all the boys in the class chocolate.
Seriously?
Mio Hayase
Family
owns cake shop
Hayase's family owns a cake shop.
She said she'd bring in some of their new stuff.
Also, Nakamura and Kawai are in the cooking club,
Mayumi Nakamura
Cooking
Club
Saki Kawai
Cooking Club
so it's likely they'll pass some out too.
You're well-informed.
Why have you been doing so much research?
Well...
Hino House
Hino-san, it's not much, but...
I got a souvenir for you!
Please have some of our dried persimmons.
Oh, thanks as always.
You're too old to be ogling that much.
Jealous? How unseemly.
I'm not jealous.
I'm super popular at school!
Then, you wanna have a match?
What?
To see who gets more chocolate this Valentine's Day.
If you win, I'll buy you whatever you want.
B-Bring it on!
That's why I can't miss getting any chocolates this year.
Your grandpa is popular with the ladies?
Of course he is!
Grandpa Hino's so cool!
He's even got a tight grip on Komiya's heart...
That old man's incredible...
Ganache Cake
Truffles
What about these?
Ganache Cake
Truffles
Chocolate ganache...
Ganache Cake
Truffles
That's too hard!
Chocolate cookies are good enough.
You can cut them into any shape you want.
What shape do you think Komiya-kun would like?
A dust cloth.
A broom and dustpan!
Think about this seriously!
I've heard that Komiya-kun likes dogs.
That seems hard...
Don't wimp out before you even start making it.
Despite appearances,
you've got a lot of rivals for Komiya-kun.
R-Really?
Chihiro-kun, you're such a good boy always going on errands.
I threw in some meat on the house.
Thanks!
You really are adorable!
I-Is that all...?
Anyway, we're rooting for you.
Do your best!
Th-Thanks...
Valentines
Even though I said that...
What should I do...?
Will I cause him trouble...?
What? You're giving papa two?
If I can't give it to him, I'll give Dad two!
Thanks, Yu!
yen
Yaah!
I-I'm sorry!
No, I'm sorry.
Here, you can have it.
Oh, thank you.
She's so pretty.
I wonder if she's buying
chocolate for Valentine's Day too?
Could it be that you are also
shopping for Valentine's Day?
Oh, yes...
Oh my, I knew it!
I am, too.
Let's both do our best, okay?
Yes!
Snack Corner
Miyako-san!
Surprised
Chihiro-kun.
Huh? Nomura-san?
Is she an acquaintance?
Yeah, we're in the same class.
Out shopping?
M-My mom told me to go buy some milk...
This milk's on sale!
Limited to two per person!
Th-Then, I guess I'll get that... one...
Oh my, oh my, oh my! Could this be...?
The milk's downstairs.
See ya!
Chihiro-kun likes milk chocolate better than dark.
What?!
Was I really that obvious?
That's so embarrassing!
I'll do my best.
My heart feels like it'll be split apart, working full blast
The number of things I want to do just keeps increasing
I speed up and turn toward you
I'm being led toward the future
February
Komiya!
Here, this is for you.
Oh, thanks!
Huh?
Sorry for not noticing...
So that's your relationship?
Idiot. It's from my sisters.
Get a clue!
Is that all?
Boring.
I thought he'd be alone in the morning...
What should I do?
Maybe I can put it in his shoebox...
But a teacher might think it's
something suspicious and confiscate it...
Morning!
Calm down.
I just have to give it to him sometime today,
so I'll look for a time when he's alone...
Somewhere...
Alone...
Here, you can have one.
Thanks!
Alone...
Alo...ne...
See ya!
Bye-bye!
He was never alone!
You think you can beat your grandpa?
Hmm...
I got a lot,
but I'm not sure...
Grandpa gets more every year as well.
What should I do? I'm like a stalker now...
See ya.
See you tomorrow.
I can give it to him now!
ba-dump
Why can I never think of what to say?
Let him know your pure
feelings with chocolate
I ended up following him all the way home...
Wh-What should I do?
I can't ring the doorbell...
Maybe I'll just go home.
Oh? Nomura-san!
What's up?
What should I do? What should I do?
He's going to think I'm weird!
I have to say something. I have to...
Um!
Huh?
A-Are you cold?
Yeah! Sure is cold today!
Anyway, what's up?
H-Here!
Uh... l-l was happy when you helped me the other day.
Th-That's all!
The other day?
This milk's on sale!
Oh!
It was
a different
"other day"
It was
a different
"other day"
It was
a different
"other day"
It was
a different
"other day"
It was
a different
"other day"
It was
a different
"other day"
It was
a different
"other day"
It was
a different
"other day"
It was a different "other day"
Nomura-san is nice.
I gave it to him!
It was a little weird, but I gave it to him!
Yay!
Oh my, the girl we saw at the supermarket?
Yeah, she said it was thanks for that day.
I was so surprised.
I'm glad.
It looks like she did her best and
was able to make her feelings known.
What about you, Miyako-san?
What?
Were you able to give yours to Keiichiro-san?
Yes,
Just like every other year...
You even made some for me? Thank you.
No change
It's fine. I'm fine as long as he accepts it...
Wow, your chocolate looks so good!
You really think so?
I think they turned out well, if I do say so myself!
Y-Yeah.
Heh, yours are all small.
What about you? Manju buns don't count!
The wrapping shows the
giver's feelings, so it counts!
What?!
Grandfather wins!
I'm coming in!
Chi-chan, here's some chocolate.
What?!
I got a lot from my clients.
I'm just sharing it with you.
Is that all?
Well, what kind of chocolate did you get?
It doesn't have anything to do with you, does it?
Come on, show me!
Jeez.
I've heard that Komiya likes dogs.
Maybe it's a monster?
It could be a Nazca geoglyph...
It's a dog!
Chi-chan, make sure you give something back in return.
I know!
Now, get out!
What should I give in return...?
Shounen Maid
Valentines from Miyako-sama
It's about time to think about what to get her in return.
What shall I give her this year?
Tastes normal.
Huh?
This is what my mom's baking tastes like.
The homemade feeling works, doesn't it?
I wonder...
What, did Komiya make these?
Gimme one!
Me too!
They're kind of dry...
Don't you think they're missing something?
If you aren't satisfied,
why don't you have him make them for you?
You live with a genius pastry chef, right?
Yeah, Madoka-san's sweets are delicious!
If you're gonna eat them anyway,
it's better if they're delicious right?
Yeah.
That's kind of frustrating, so no!
He hates losing...
I see...
You're worried about what to give in return for White Day.
Yeah...
I think they'll be happy with something homemade.
I usually choose something from a store though...
A store, huh...?
But this year, I'm a bit stumped.
Why?
Actually, Madoka-sama said...
What? Only elementary schoolers
are happy with stuffed animals, right?
That is what he pointed out...
I-I see...
But I don't know how to find out what high school girls like...
I have absolutely no idea...
I think she'll be happy with
whatever Keiichiro-san gives her, though...
Oh, right.
Madoka-sama gives homemade gifts every year, you know.
Why don't you ask him for advice?
Stare...
D-Did you need something?
Are you baking?
Yeah, I thought it was about time
to decide what I'd make for White Day.
Am I in the way?
You're fine, you're fine.
It's hard to bake like this.
Clean up as you bake!
I'm sorry!
Chi-chan, which one do you think is best?
Think about that after you've cleaned up!
Don't say that. Have a taste.
It's good.
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Kind
of angry
Tastes good
Hey...
Hm? What is it?
Um... Can you teach me how to bake?
Sure!
Put off
Well, shall we start?
What're these clothes?
They're like a pastry chef's, right?
I thought something like this might happen,
so I prepared matching outfits!
You know what...
What will you make, Chi-chan?
I've decided to make macarons.
What are macarons?
These things.
They look cute, so girls really like them.
Do you think I can make them, too?
That's what I'm here for!
Now first, separate the egg yolks from the egg whites.
Okay.
Freeze the egg whites.
What? We're not making them now?
When egg whites are fresh,
they can make the batter runny.
Really?
But even if I say that, we can't wait.
Huh?
So here's some I froze yesterday.
Take that out first!
And then measure the ingredients...
Put the dry ingredients together and sift...
Then put them into the fridge.
Again?
Yep! It's like a neat science experiment.
Making the
Meringue
If you mess up the measurements
just a little, that will ruin it too.
Making the
Meringue
Bad example
There's only a little left, so I'll put it all in.
Now, this next part is important.
Once you finish mixing the ingredients,
it's time for the macaronage.
Maca-what?
In other words, swirly twirly time!
"Swirly twirly"?
Like this...
L-Like this?
More floopy and swirly!
Can you use real words?
Scattered
What's the matter?
Nothing... I might be having an identity crisis.
They look pretty good for your first time.
Really...?
They don't have to be perfect.
If the gift is from the heart,
they'll still be happy even if the shape isn't perfect, right?
That's true, but...
If you're not satisfied,
then you can also try making it nice another way.
What's that?
A handmade pouch.
If you put them in these,
they'll look a lot more charming.
They're mostly made from cloth scraps,
so it's like killing two birds with one stone.
Do you have more scraps?
I can only make a drawstring pouch, though.
I should at least look for a cuter pattern.
Scraps
What's this? Cats?
That guy really likes cats, huh?
All right.
So, you were doing that until morning?
Are you okay?
Yeah sure...
Give this to your older sisters and Hana-chan.
Okay, thank you.
Nomura-san...
Y-Yes?
Thanks for the gift on Valentine's Day.
Th-Thanks...
All right!
Isn't that great, Yu-chan?
Yeah...
Oh my, this is Antaro, isn't it?
It's adorable!
Thank you, Chihiro-kun.
Don't mention it.
By the way...
What's that bear...?
It's a White Day present from Keiichiro-sama!
He ended up giving her a stuffed animal anyway?!
He said this chain at its neck is also a bracelet.
It's my first time receiving jewelry from Keiichiro-sama.
That's great!
Yes!
Come in.
Scraps
Thanks for this.
Sure. Were you able to make some cute pouches?
Well, I'm not sure if they were cute or not...
I wish I could've seen them.
Oh!
Next time, I'll teach you how to gather frills.
No, it's okay.
What?
Well, I'm going to sleep now.
Night.
Night!
Huh?
Thanks for teaching me. It was a big help.
He's so conscientious.
I wonder if he likes monsters...?
Reference Material
Episode 8.5
Women Should Be Brave,
and Men Should Be Winsome?
Chocolate
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
I heard from Chihiro-kun you
have an embarrassing picture of me.
Yup, I do. Wanna see?
Shocked
Will you trade with this?
Oh, a cat photo book! Sure, sure! Here!
Wh-When did you take this picture?!
I forgot!
Hey, hey, don't you think this black cat is cute?
Kuromame?
You even know its name?
Are you friends?
Um, well...
Mental Image
Next time, "One Good Turn Deserves Another".
One Good Turn Deserves Another
Everyone, please watch.
You changed the subject!
Please watch!