All right, I'm done!
Next is—
U-Um...
I didn't do it on purpose.
Don't try to do anything!
I'm sorry!
Jeez, how dirty do you have
to make things before you're happy?
Yes?
Who's there...?
Oh, what a cute little helper.
Um...
You're a boy?
Oh, Miyako?
I apologize for coming without notice, Madoka-onii-sama.
"Madoka-nii-sama"?
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
Are you running away from home again?
That's because Father never listens to anything I say!
Running away here every time
you fight isn't helping, though, is it?
B-But...
"Nii-sama"?
Is she your little sister?
Oh, no, no. She's—
Madoka-sama.
About the details of the bridal fair—
Miyako-sama?
Keiichirou-sama!
Will you listen to this?
To what, may I ask?
My father does not think about my feelings one bit!
What's she talking about?
Well, she's my—
Madoka-nii-sama, you don't
intend to marry me either, do you?
Underage
I think you're getting the wrong idea, Chihiro.
My...?
Good for
nothing?
This is the guy, Officer!
He's a pervert
Kidnapper
Marriage scam?
Chihiro?
Then you're Chiyo-nee-sama's son?
I apologize for not introducing myself sooner.
My name is Ootori Miyako.
Grandfather Takatori was good friends
with the last head of the Ootori family...
...so it's like we've been stuck with each other.
That's not true.
Um, I'm Komiya Chihiro.
Nice to meet you, Chihiro-kun.
By the way, why are you wearing such a charming outfit?
Wait... Why am I wearing clothes like this again?
Can't help...
Chihiro-kun...
That's strange...
That's because Chihiro works as a housekeeper here!
Oh my, but he's still a child.
Why?
That's because...
This will be your home starting today!
Come, be spoiled as much as you want!
No, I cannot just be in your debt!
Please allow me to work, as well!
Oh, Chihiro!
Uncle Madoka-sama!
Uncle Madoka-sama! You're wonderful!
Oh my, how admirable!
Ugh, I don't want to deal with these people anymore...
How extraordinary.
Chihiro's already independent!
Compared to him, I'm...
That's true.
Keiichirou also relies on Chihiro a lot as well, right?
Right?
Yes.
Of course.
I cannot continue like this.
In order to get Father to recognize me,
I must become a dependable person.
I will show him I can become independent, too!
Just like Chihiro-kun.
Therefore...
...I am counting on your guidance, Sensei!
Huh?
Hu
h
?
Now, what shall we begin with, Sensei?
Do your best, Chi-chan!
You be quiet.
Then, let's start with cleaning.
Please take those stairs.
Yes!
Sweep. Sweep. Sweep.
Start from the top...
Wring the water out of the mop first!
Y-Yes!
Don't wipe the windows with a dust cloth!
I-I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Watch your step!
Where's the dust cloth?
They're so lively.
Oh, be careful!
Are you hurt?
No.
I'm no good, am I?
Miyako-sama.
Are you all right?
Keiichirou-sama!
Yes, I'm fine!
I will see this through to the end!
I-Is that right?
Well, I'll get going now.
Good work today.
Have a nice evening, Keiichirou-sama!
Now Sensei, what's next?
You're so easy to read...
I was thinking about making dinner soon...
Very well, sir!
Wow...
At first, I only knew how to bake sweets,
but I practiced so that I could cook meals, as well.
I see.
Then, can I leave the cooking to you?
Yes!
Wow, did you make all this Miyako?
Yum, it's delicious!
Thank you very much!
By the way, where's Chihiro?
Yeah... about that.
He said he was full from
tasting the food, so he would eat later...
By the way, I'm the one who taught her how to bake.
Is that right?!
Shall I help?
No, it's fine, it'll be faster if I do it myself.
In fact, make sure you don't get in my way.
Okay...
Tsk...
Um, I will clean, as well!
He said class is over for today.
See you tomorrow.
Yep.
Did major
cleaning by accident.
I worked a little too hard.
Did major
cleaning by accident.
You'll catch a cold.
Chihiro-kun...
You were working until this late?
O-Oh, uh...
I got a little carried away...
I'm sorry.
I have caused you only trouble.
Do you suppose I should do what my Father says after all?
You know...
...because of an agreement between our families,
I am to marry Madoka-nii-sama when I turn sixteen.
Nii-sama is a wonderful person.
But...
...when I said I at least wanted to choose
who to marry myself, I was called selfish.
That's not selfish!
You're being forced to marry that?
Chi... hi... ro!
That
Why are you being punished like that?
Chihiro-kun, you're so kind!
That
Anyway Miyako-san, you like Keiichirou-san, right?
How did you know?!
No, "why"?
Is this what it means to have hidden love show on your face?
Blush
You were hiding it?
You were doing the housework training
because you wanted Keiichirou-san to see it, right?
Th-That's... true... but...
I made so many mistakes...
If I continue to act selfishly and end up
causing even Keiichirou-sama trouble, then I...
"You can't betray yourself.
In order to live, compromise is necessary...
...but don't do anything that goes against your heart."
My mom said that.
If you give up from the start, then you can't
even win what you have a chance of winning.
But I can't do anything.
You made a proper dinner.
And it was delicious.
Once you learn how to clean as you cook, you'll be golden.
Chihiro-kun...
You're right.
I can't give up on myself, can I?
Yeah.
Yes.
It looks like things will be fine now.
Please come pick her up tomorrow.
Okay, and turn!
Oh, you're so cute!
From now on, please wear that and do your best.
Thank you very much, Madoka-nii-sama!
He makes things like that really fast, huh?
Oh, I'll get it.
I also made these!
Miyako cookies and Keiichirou cookies!
Wow, they're lovely!
Right?
Don't tell me you left the kitchen a mess again?!
Well, you know, I only spilled a little flour...
What do you mean, "a little"?!
I just cleaned it!
I'm sorry!
Chihiro, calm down!
I don't know what to do about Miyako.
She is causing you problems, as well, isn't she?
Chi-chan, stop it!
Miyako, I've come for—
Father?
Wh-What is this...?
What is the meaning of this, Madoka-kun?
I like this kind of thing.
What about it?
W-We're going home, Miyako!
Wait, Father... Why...?
Madoka-kun, it appears I misjudged you.
I am calling off your engagement to Miyako!
Aren't you glad you realized your mistake?
Miyako, you are never to see that deviant again!
That's mean, Father!
Madoka-nii-sama is not a devian—
Madoka-nii-sama!
Chihiro-kun!
Keiichirou-sama...!
That was in bad taste.
You're mean too, Chi-chan.
You could've refused normally, idiot!
What?
But I worked so hard...
Shounen Maid
Oh, it's Komiya.
Hey, Komiya!
I was worried since I didn't see you at school.
You moved in with a relative?
That's great.
Yeah.
Sorry, I didn't get a chance to tell you guys.
I'll be back at school after the Golden Week holidays.
Okay.
Hey, what kind of house do you live in now?
Is your relative nice?
About that.
Can you believe he put me in a mai—
Wait, I can't say it.
If they find out about that, they'll laugh at me.
T
h
a
t
"Mai" what?
Ma— Maybe it's not that bad.
It's super normal, so don't worry.
Okay?
Really?
Komiya, you're hiding something, aren't you?
Wha...?
You're not forcing yourself at your new place, are you?
N-No, I'm not!
If you have any problems, make sure you—
No, no.
There are no problems! I'm super fine!
W-Well, I have to get ready for dinner, so...
Hey, Komiya!
I feel like I made them worried for some reason....
...but I didn't lie, right?
Yeah.
What a huge house!
He was taken in by the person who owns this house?
Then there's nothing to worry about, right?
Yeah, let's go home.
Komiya?!
Well?
Where should I start?
Pretend you didn't see this...
Can't.
You said you were fine, right?
Were you lying?
N-No, I wasn't!
Then, what's with those clothes?
They're making you work, right?
No, that's not it! I'm the one who—
If you don't want to be indebted to the Takatori family,
then we can arrange for some give-and-take instead.
I'm the one who was acting selfish...
Cosplaying's your hobby?
That's unexpected.
Yeah.
No, it can't be helped!
This is my uniform!
Uniform?
Well, it's fine as long as you're okay.
Those clothes are fine, too.
They don't look that bad on you.
You don't need to make me feel better...
We're not going to make fun of you
for something like that after all this time.
So don't force yourself or lie or trick us.
Everyone's worried about you, you know.
Yup, yup.
It's important to have friends.
Oh, I'm Chihiro's uncle.
Nice to meet YOU—
How. Many times. Do I. Have to tell you?
Don't. Come in. Without permission!
Stupid! Bastard!
See ya!
See you at school!
Bye-bye!
They're good kids, huh?
Yeah.
I'll invite them over properly next time.
Okay!
Then, I'll do my best to entertain them!
You don't have to be so eager!
I have finished, Sensei.
Food's done.
Cleanup's done.
Good, you pass!
Thank you very much!
Yes, yes, that's great.
By the way...
Is lunch ready yet?
The next goal will be to finish in a timely manner.
Yes!
A cooking class every Sunday, huh?
Miiyako's sure working hard.
Yeah.
By the way, is Keiichirou off on Sundays?
I wonder if he'd come just to eat?
My dream is to have Keiichirou-sama eat my cooking one day.
I see.
How admirable.
Well, I'm sure Keiichirou would come if we asked him to...
...but if you're worried,
you can definitely get him with pudding!
Oh, pudding...
Huh?
Pudding?
Unexpected...
That's right. He likes pudding.
Isn't that cute?
Is that right?
But, it's not a meal or a side dish...
If we make that dessert—
He also likes sushi, but it has to
be something Miyako can make...
Wait.
Now that I think about it,
I don't know what foods this guy likes.
Shocked
Even though I cook for him every day...
Foods Madoka likes
All right...
There seems to be more food than usual today.
I made a little too much.
You don't have to eat all of it.
Let's eat!
Even if he doesn't have likes or dislikes,
he should at least have taste preferences.
Thanks for the food!
Why are you angry?
I'm not angry!
What tasted the best?
Everything!
That's what I thought you'd say,
but it's annoying to really be told that!
What I like to eat?
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
Well, I was just thinking that I'd never asked you about it...
Is that all?
I like whatever you make, Chihiro!
That's annoying!
What?
If you say everything's good,
then I won't have any motivation to cook.
Even if you say that...
Isn't there anything?
Anything you want to eat, or want me to make for you?
Then, a bento!
You start school again tomorrow,
so it'd be nice to have one for lunch.
Bento, huh?
Wait, that has nothing to do with the kind of food he likes!
Tricked!!
Oh well, I'll just make something.
I'll put in the leftover stewed
chicken and vegetables from dinner,
and I have hamburger, so I can make meatballs.
There was salmon, too...
It's not very creative, but I can
make octopus-shaped hot dogs...
Other than that, bentos have...
Rolled omelets...
Now that I think about it, I've never made them before.
What do you think?
Isn't it pretty?
Wow...
Why are you only good at making rolled omelets?
Because I practiced!
Practicing making other food then, too.
If you chase two rabbits,
you won't catch either one Chihiro.
What does that mean?
Teach me the trick, too.
No! Then I won't have anything to do.
No one else can be in charge of the rolled omelets.
When did you become "in charge" of them?
Why did you only practice making rolled omelets?
That's because...
Why are you sleeping here?!
In the end, she never taught me how to make rolled omelets...
I should've had her teach me back then, after all...
I'll be the substitute rolled omelet cook today.
Morning...
Morning.
Is this the bento?
Yeah.
Yay! Thanks!
Sorry.
What's wrong?
I messed up.
Oh?
Hey, don't open it now!
The rolled omelets...
I couldn't make them pretty like Mom did...
Because I didn't learn how to make them properly.
Yum. It's good.
Don't eat it now!
It tastes burnt, doesn't it?
When we were little,
we used to play picnic in the garden all the time.
Nee-san would make a bento, but it would only have weirdly-shaped rice balls and burnt rolled omelets.
Th-This is...
The whole thing is black...
What?!
Never mind the rice balls,
the rolled omelets were a disaster.
There was too much sugar, and it was
hard to tell if they were sweet or bitter.
But you know, I actually liked them.
Why did you only practice making rolled omelets?
That's because...
...it was frustrating to have my
failures eaten like they were delicious.
I see...
She learned how to cook them nicely.
I'll practice, too.
I'll feed you really nice-looking ones,
not those failures, you'll see!
'Kay...
So...
...you have to be the taste tester, Madoka!
With pleasure.
So the other party would like to directly...
Glance!
Madoka-sama?
Glance! Glance!
Madoka-sama!
Are you listening?
What, is it already lunch?
Can I eat my bento?
If you are that hungry, then please do.
Yay!
Time to eat!
Oh right.
Come over and eat with us this Sunday.
There'll be pudding.
Pudding?!
And so, here are my failed attempts.
Everyone, help me get rid of them!
You told us to skip breakfast for this?
Episode 2
Failure is the
Mother of Success
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
Komiya, do you know what the girls in class call you?
No.
They say you're the #1 boy they'd want for a bride!
What? Why?
I know, right?
You're supposed to be the groom.
Please adopt me
I've already found the perfect partner for you!
What? Who?
Here's a hint! Next time,
in "Feed a Dog for Three Days and
He Will Remember It for Three Years,"
she may or may not appear!
If she won't appear, then don't say it!
The answer is, ta-da—
Feed a Dog for Three Days and
He Will Remember it for Three Years
My little sister, Hino Hanako!
Don't reveal it!
Look forward to it!