To Chi-chan
What is it...?
How did... you know...
...what I wanted?
Um... it's probably because it was Santa.
Santa's amazing!
Yeah, because he's Santa!
Wow... Wow!
Aren't you glad he likes it?
It's so light! Wow...!
Yeah, but I wanted to give him something more fun...
But with a home shopping catalog
that marked up, it's hard to ignore, you know?
He even circled things in red pen.
But you know...
Hello?
Oh, hey.
Hm? Play video games at Hino's house?
Sorry, I can't today.
I'm doing some major cleaning!
Was this really okay...
...for an elementary schooler?
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
Komiya
Komiya said he's doing major cleaning.
What, today?
It's only the 25th.
Man, and I got a new game, too.
That house is big,
so it's a lot of work to clean it.
Yeah...
Then I wonder if he canplay if he finishes cleaning?
You're here to help?
It's a lot of work to do
major cleaning by yourself, right?
Yeah, it'll be faster if we all do it together, right?
And then, when it's done, we can play!
Four-on-four battle!
Okay!
CHRISTMAS TREE
Decorations
Hino's not with you guys?
He said he forgot something
at home, so he went to go get it.
I see.
Then here. Aprons.
You don't have any, right?
Your clothes will get dirty if
you don't wear one, so you can use mine.
It's okay if they get dirty...
No, it's not.
They'll get all dusty.
But those frills...
It's fine!
Enlightened
Once you're cleaning,
the frills don't matter anymore...
Enlightened
You're too used to it!
Hello!
Just laugh!
It's even more annoying if you don't!
No, no, it looks good on you guys.
For real.
You're wearing one too, Hino.
I thought it might turn out like this,
so I brought one from home.
No fair!
Well!
What should we start with?
Let's finish this quickly.
Okay, then first—
Hello!
I'll help, too!
There's a lot of heavy lifting
involved with major cleaning, right?
Really?
Yeah.
Then...
Important Things
Put away the things in that mountain.
Keiichirou-san, will you help us with the heavy stuff?
Okay.
What about this?
Um, let's see...
Ostracized...
I've been excluded...
Now then, with my pudding power—
Oh, wait a sec.
Dust off the top before you move it.
Oh, sorry.
Don't scrub too hard, let the cleaner soak first.
Oh, okay.
Do the roller last!
Don't play with the detergent!
Wipe the windows from the corners to the middle.
Once it's half dry, wipe it with a dry cloth.
Okay, okay.
I wonder if we'll ever finish...
Looks like it'll take a while.
Jeez, I've got no other choice.
I'll call in some backup.
Backup?
Hello.
Miyako-san?
What's up?
I heard from Hino-kun that you were cleaning.
That guy...
Oh, you're here!
Hello, everyone!
Oh?
Those outfits...
These are...
Oh, no, it's...
Now they're perfect!
Don't laugh!
Um, you'd be a big help,
but are you sure about this?
Leave it to me!
As Chihiro-kun's first disciple,
I will show you how it's done!
Now then, this flooring...
Oh, dilute the detergent before using it.
R-Right!
Make sure you squeeze out the water first!
Right!
Move backwards when wiping the floor!
Right...
And wipe along the grain of the boards.
R-Right!
The floors well get damaged if left wet, so dry them quickly.
R-Right—
I'll bring some cloths, so just don't move!
Now that I think about it,
I haven't been trained in cleaning yet...
Don't worry about it.
Are you all right?
We're fine.
We'll take care of this,
so you can go do something else.
Right, Miyako-san?
Oh, yes! I know what to do now,
and if everyone helps, we should be fine.
Okay.
Then I'll leave the rest to you.
Okay!
Okay.
I'll change the water.
Okay!
So should I wipe it dry now?
Yes, please!
We're done...
Everyone, thanks for your hard work.
Thanks, guys.
No prob!
Now we can play starting tomorrow, right?
Yeah!
All that's left is the laundry
and polishing the stainless steel in the kitchen...
You're not done yet?
Let's play!
Speaking of which, where's Madoka?
Oh, Madoka-sama came out of his room,
so I urged him to his workroom.
Here you go.
I thought it would be good for him
to clean the places only he could do.
Good job, Keiichirou-san!
That's called being a demon!
Thanks for your hard work, everyone.
Here are some homemade sweets.
Don't tell me you—
Chi-chan, your face is scary!
Jeez, I cleaned everything up today.
What?!
It's true that it's not messy, like it usually is.
Heh-heh.
Because it's cleaning day!
I can do anything if I put my mind to it!
Madoka-nii-sama, you're amazing!
Praise me more!
Don't try to trick me by throwing everything away!
Ow!
I thought it'd take longer.
Aren't you glad everyone came?
It was more fun than doing it by yourself, right?
Yeah.
Well, now you have to rest properly.
Huh?
The end of the year is busy so you
can have a proper rest on New Year's.
It's winter vacation too,
so why don't we go somewhere?
"Somewhere"?
You know, like on a trip.
Hino said that's what long breaks are for.
That guy again?
Stop doing everything Hino tells you.
Jeez, even though you're a shut-in.
You don't have to force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself.
Let's go visit somewhere together, Chihiro.
'Kay.
Then, I won't get my hopes up.
To Chi-chan
You should!
Shounen Maid
Wow, it's snow!
Keiichirou-san, how much
longer until we get to the cabin?
Let's see... about 30 minutes.
I'm looking forward to
celebrating the new year with everyone!
Right?
Hino-kun, you don't need to stay with your family?
It's fine, it's fine.
I'm lucky I get to skip the cleaning!
Oh my!
Hey...
Chihiro, you have been quiet for a while.
Are you all right?
What should I do...?
I think I left the door to the trash area unlocked...
There's nothing but trash in there, so it's fine!
No, it's not!
Someone or something might get into it!
Jeez, just forget about the house for now!
It looks like a real cabin.
Yeah, it does.
I mean, it is a cabin...
There's a stove!
There's an attic!
There's a kotatsu!
It's totally like a cabin!
By what standards?
This is my first time visiting here, as well.
It's been a while for me, too.
I came a lot with Nee-san as a kid, though.
It's been a while?
Then...
...we have to start with cleaning, right?!
There's a caretaker, so you don't have to worry about it.
Disappointed...
Um, sorry.
Are you stupid?
Didn't we come to play?
Why aren't you playing?
Now you have done it!
I'm glad I had Hino-kun come...
Wait up!
A pond?
Wow, it's totally frozen.
It won't crack?
Don't worry.
It looks like the caretaker
cleaned it up for us.
There are shoes prepared, too.
Would you like to skate?
That sounds good!
Yeah, let's do it!
Huh?!
Um, I've never skated before...
Oh my, then I'm the teacher today, aren't I?
Don't worry, you'll be able to skate in no time!
R-Right...
Impossible...
Seriously, it's impossible...
Chihiro-kun, you're like a newborn deer.
Look this way.
Let's start by practicing pushing out on one leg.
I can't do it!
Do your best!
Hino, you little—
Stop me...!
Chihiro-kun, look this way please!
I can't!
Tighten your stomach.
I can't...
Chi-chan, do your best!
Madoka-san, you're not gonna skate?
Well, you know... I'm his guardian, so I have to watch...
Wh-Wh-What...?!
Madoka's so uncool.
I don't want to hear that from you, Chi-chan!
Stop... me...!
Keiichirou, you demon!
All right.
I'll learn to skate better than Madoka!
Oh my!
Hino, you little—
I got some good pictures.
I wonder if he'll be all right?
I'm sure he'll get used to it soon.
Why don't you leave the rest
to Hino-kun and go skate, Miyako-sama?
Right...
U-Um, Keiichirou-sama...
...I'm not good at skating backwards.
If it's not too much trouble,
w-will you give me some advice?
It's easy once you get the hang of it.
If you'll have me, shall I teach you?
Yes!
Sniff.
I'll never put on skates again.
I learned to skate a little.
Lucky you...
I'm starving!
It's hot pot!
Oh? When was this prepared?
Ah, that was the caretaker too.
The caretaker always makes the bed, lights the stove,
and makes other preparations before anyone notices.
"Before anyone notices"?
Actually, I've never seen the caretaker's face...
There are fairies like that, aren't there?
Then first, let's turn the fire on, and—
Please wait!
Chihiro-kun, you're on vacation, so you should rest.
Please leave everything to me white we're here.
But...
Don't worry.
I won't burn anything anymore!
It's fine once in a while, isn't it?
Yeah.
Let's see.
We can put them in once the water boils, right?
Hold on, take out the kelp for soup stock—
That's annoying.
Let's eat already!
You can just throw
everything in for hot pot, and it'll cook.
Is that right?
Then—
How bold.
It's fine, as long as it's edible.
If we put it all in, it'll overflow, huh?
We can just put more in after
we've eaten some to make space.
Take out the kelp...
I see!
You have to skim off the top...
Here you are.
Go ahead, Chihiro-kun.
Th... Thanks...
Delish!
It's delicious!
Thanks for the food!
I ate so much!
Hot pot's fun, isn't it?
Once we clean up, let's play a game!
Okay!
Oh, Chihiro-kun.
I'll take the dishes.
No, it's...
...on my way to the bathroom!
Chihiro-kun!
Doesn't it seem to be
making him more stressed?
He seems bored.
You don't have to force him to rest.
If he wants to do it, why don't you let him?
But...
He's always taking care of us.
I want to pay him back once in a while...
I'm telling you...
There's a better way to make him happy.
Komiya!
What is it?
Get me a drink!
What do you want?
Um, cola! With ice!
Okay, okay.
Here.
Thank you, Komiya-sama!
Komiya, you angel!
Quiet, that's gross.
Stop that, it's gonna spill.
Um...
I'd like some tea...
Oh, me too!
I guess I can't relax unless
I drink the tea you make, Chi-chan.
The tea you make tastes
better than mine anyway. Right?
J-Jeez, I guess it can't be helped.
Here.
Thanks!
Thank you!
Thank you.
C-Can I also wash the dishes...?
Uh, sure.
Wash as much as you want.
Yay!
Oh, I'll help!
He's such a handful...
I'm sorry.
Then, let's leave the cleaning up to the hard workers.
Ta-da!
How about it?
This is unusual.
Once in a while...
Wait, you can't have any Hino-kun.
We'll get in trouble...
...with Chihiro-kun.
The adults should be the ones getting mad...
The annual end-of-the-year
dream song battle! Next up is...
Hello!
Oh, they're on!
Everyone, are you watching?
Oh, it's Ryuji-san!
It's their first time on the show,
so he seems really into it!
Really?
Put love on the song—
—and let it reach everyone's hearts.
We're—
Uchoten Boys!
Frills on traditional Japanese clothes...?
Did you design those clothes as well, Madoka-san?
Yeah.
How original!
To all the people who have supported us—
Here's our thanks—
As we sing our song—
"Clear Blue Heart"!
Wow, amazing!
That's no good, this isn't either.
What in the word do you want to do?
They're really into it.
Who are you? Who are you to me?
I want to ask you just once
If your heart hurts and is in pain,
then I'll be your medicine
I don't need a love...
I fell asleep...
Oh, you're awake, Chi-chan?
Madoka, what're you doing?
Waiting for the first sunrise.
Let's watch it together, Chi-chan.
Okay.
It's already gotten pretty bright,
so the sun should be coming up soon.
It feels like it's been a while since I did this.
Really?
I snuck out when I was little with Nee-san.
We'd wrap ourselves in a blanket,
and sit next to each other out here.
Here?
Yup.
I watched the first sunrise with Mom until last year.
From the small window of our apartment...
...just the two of us.
And then, when the sun appears—
I'm counting on you this year, too!
Whoever says it first wins, right?
You did it, too?
Yeah, we sure did.
There's no point in winning or losing though.
I guess not.
Wanna come again next year?
Let's watch the sunrise here together again.
Yeah.
Long
Life
All right, I'm done!
You look really pretty!
Thank you very much!
Why do you look so proud of yourself, Madoka?
Look this way.
Oh, okay.
Hey, by the way...
...what's with this New Year's food?
Oh, I asked our chef to make some...
Um, Mom also made me bring some...
I also made some just in case.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I ordered some.
I can't believe you of all people forgot to
ask others what they were doing, Keiichirou...
And, there's also...
Here's some rice cake soup
Please reheat the soup
and put in the rice cakes
Caretaker
...rice cake soup already made in the kitchen.
The caretaker again?!
What should we do?
We'll just have to gain New Year's weight together.
Long
Life
Right...
Well then...
Let's take a picture first before we get fat.
Ready.
Shall we take another
picture after we eat to compare?
What?!
N-Not after we eat...
Well then, I'm taking it!
Episode 8
The Devil Scoffs When You Talk of Next Year
Ha
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
Madoka-nii-sama, it's almost Valentines day right?
First it was osechi and mochi, next is chocolate!
Yep!
Then next is White Day when I can bake cookies and macrons!
It's a bit of a problem though...
Huh?
Lately I've been eating a lot of Chi-chan's
amazing food and now my pants are getting tighter.
Not a problem, we can take Antarou out for walks together.
That's not going to happen!
Next time, "Women should be brave, and Men should be Winsome?"
Women Should Be Brave,
and Men Should Be Winsome?
I'll try to get through life by being winsome too!
Tehe!
Please watch!
Nom nom.