I'm Komiya Chihiro.
I'm in fifth grade.
After my mom passed away,
I came to live here at Madoka Takatori's house.
But it doesn't sit well with me to be a freeloader!
Leave all the cleaning, cooking, laundry, and housework to me!
Those who do not work shall not eat
! !
That's right.
Those who do not work shall not eat
! !
Mom said it too.
Those who do not work shall not eat
! !
"Those who do not work shall not eat."
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
All right!
What should I make for breakfast?
I made french toast yesterday,
so maybe Japanese food today?
I can fry some salmon and—
That guy left the door open...
Good morni—
I can't take it anymore!
Today's the day I'm gonna make you let me do it, Madoka!
W-Wait a minute, Chihiro!
That's not what we agreed on!
Wh-What's the matter?
Keiichirou, help!
Chihiro's invading my room!
I-Invading?!
Don't make it sound so bad!
It's not like I want to do
something like this, either.
Madoka, you're already an adult,
so I thought I should at least make
you clean your own room yourself, but—
Oh, is that what you're talking about?
But then, I saw...
...that guy in Madoka's room—
The Bearded Baron!
The Bearded Baron?!
Hello. Renaissance!
The Bearded Baron: Black, fast, and resilient "King of Pests."
The Bearded Baron
Black, fast, and resilient
The king of pests
A word used by the Komiya family
A word used by the Komiya family.
I can't believe the Bearded Baron is in a house that I clean...
I won't allow it!
I will exterminate him!
I'll clean every corner!
No...! Stop it...!
I won't listen to you even if you cry!
That's mean! That's mean...
Before Madoka-sama's room gets invaded,
roach— I mean, beardead baron motels must be setup.
Jeez.
I can't believe this house still had such an uncivilized land.
Shall I help?
I'm good.
It's just this room, anyway.
Keiichirou-san, you stand guard over Madoka.
Very well.
Even though I know it's a toy,
I'm so scared that I can't open the door...
All right! Let's do this!
He's like a fish in water.
But man, how did things get so messy in here?
Jeez...
What's this?
A present?
It's empty?
It's just wrapping paper?
Why?!
Now that I'm looking for them, I see them everywhere...
What's wrong with him?!
I will see you tomorrow, then.
What'd you think?
It's nice and clean now, right?
It looks like someone else's room now...
From now on, make sure you clean properly.
Where are the things that were over here?
The books are on the bookshelves,
the stationery items are in the drawers,
the clothes are in the laundry,
and all the trash has been thrown away.
Trash...
Can you stop leaving your trash all over the place?
And make sure you bring out your laundry every day!
'Kay.
I'm done.
A-Are you feeling okay?
Yeah.
Did I mess up on the seasoning?
I think it tastes good, though...
I'm going back to my room.
Oh, wait!
There are too many clean clothes,
so they might not all fit in the closet in your room.
Oh, you can throw them away.
Then, choose the ones you don't wear—
I don't want to bother with it, so you can choose.
Hey!
At least do that yourself—
What's his deal?
What?
A second-hand clothes shop?
Yeah.
There are a lot of clothes Madoka doesn't wear,
and it's a waste to throw them away.
Then, shall I drive you?
Will you?
I often drive Madoka-sama
around on his personal business.
Thanks!
Um, Keiichirou-san...
...do you think Madoka's acting weird?
He's been the same as usual.
Why?
He's been kind of down since yesterday...
Ah—
Perhaps it's because he was scolded yesterday?
Maybe it was cruel to force my cleaning on him...
I think he got what he deserved, though.
Really?
In the first place,
Madoka-sama can never throw anything away.
He can't throw things away?
Yes. Especially when it comes to presents,
he puts up even the wrapping paper as decoration.
Look, look, Keiichirou!
The present doubled!
What was
inside
Empty
He even retied the ribbon neatly.
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
Empty
What was
inside
He's too dexterous for his own good...
Really...
That's because Madoka-sama
cherishes the fact that he received a present
more than the object he actually received.
It's trash, right...?
But...
Mom!
Hm?
Hey, can I throw away this stuff that's been on the fridge forever?
1/2 Daikon
Carrots
Oh, you can't throw that away!
You can't! It's a memento!
A memento?
That's right.
It's the note from your first errand.
I wrote it in kanji by accident...
...and you couldn't read kanji yet, so you were on the verge of tears.
You were so cute!
What the heck?
There are others, too.
Like this, which is the first time you wrote your name.
Are these letters?!
And this is the first time you drew me.
It's scary!
But why are they stuck on the fridge?
Isn't it nice to be able to see them easily?
But the fridge is covered with papers now.
I want to put the schedule of school lunches up...
It's fine!
Just put it on top!
Your mom's a genius!
What?!
Is this a family-wide issue?
It just looks like trash to me...
But...
All right.
Keiichirou-san!
I will assist you.
But your clothes will get dirty—
I don't mind.
It's faster if we split up the work.
Now, let's do our best to find them.
Okay.
Um...
They were all scrunched up, so I ironed them...
...but then I couldn't put them back to their original shape.
Sorry.
I remember their shapes, so it's fine.
They're so neat now.
Thanks, Chihiro!
Also—
It was your fault for putting important things with the trash.
Ah, you're in lecture mode already?!
Important Things
Put your important things in their proper place or in this box.
Then, I won't throw them away.
He's like a mom.
I can't fit everything in such a small box!
Organize them so they will fit!
By the way. if they stick out, I'm throwing them away.
Tyrant!
Do your best.
I won't.
Important Things
I said, do it.
I won't.
Important Things
Enough!
Shounen Maid
Important Things
I won't!
Just do it!
Important Things
Put in the eggs and sugar, milk, and vanilla essence—
Homemade Sweets
And mix well, right?
After you finish mixing, use the strainer.
Okay, Sensei!
Apparently, straining it twice will make it smoother and better.
Okay!
Now that I think about it,
when do we put in the caramel sauce?
Oh, we should have put it into the cup first...
Wait a minute—
It's getting absorbed nicely.
Even if you put it in after,
its relative density makes it sink to the bottom.
I don't make desserts often, so I didn't know either.
Bake them in the oven for thirty minutes.
Once they are cool to the touch,
wrap them in plastic and
let them cool completely in the fridge.
Oh, the caramel sauce didn't mix
with the pudding and solidified nicely.
Yeah, isn't that great?
Yes!
But...
What is it?
There are pores.
Pores?
su (ambiguous)
su (pores)
Those spots on the surface.
Oh my!
This happens to savory egg custard too...
It worsens the flavor and texture.
How can they be prevented?
By adjusting the heat while steaming...
You just have to get used to it.
It seems easy, but it's hard to make pudding well, isn't it?
Yup.
Ignoring the texture, it tastes pretty good.
Do your best!
Madoka-nii-sama!
Cheer Keiichirou up...
...with his favorite food, pudding.
Okay!
It looks like he's under a lot of stress from work.
Poor guy.
And you just so happen to be his boss, Madoka.
I'll make Keiichirou-sama
smile with my homemade pudding!
Do your best!
A tea party hosted by Miyako-sama?
Yeah, next Sunday.
That's fine...
Her cooking and baking have gotten a lot better!
Recently, I haven't had to help her much at all.
Is that right?
That's good to hear.
At any rate,
Miyako-sama seems to be working very hard.
I wonder if she wants to be a chef...
Falling
Falling...
No, I'm sure she's trying to be a bride...
...of a certain someone.
Oh. She's very girlish.
So dense!
His reaction's so dense!
Keiichirou-sama!
Even though she's being so obvious...
Unless he noticed but is
pretending he doesn't know?
Huh?
Keiichirou-san's planner?
It's unusual for him to forget his things.
There was a girl's picture in his planner?
That must be his girlfriend or
a girl he likes who doesn't like him back.
But it looks like a pretty old picture...
And she looked like she was in junior high school...
Doesn't that just mean he's known her for that long?
What should I do?
I found out something awful...
Oh...
They turned out nice.
Yes!
It was worth practicing at home.
I know just the right temperature now!
Sh-Should I tell her?
No, but Keiichirou-san hasn't said anything either.
So I can't be the one to expose it...
But, but—
Miyako-san is trying so hard and it'd
be sad if she never had a chance from the start.
It'd be better sooner rather than later...
Spin
No, but, but—
Sensei?
Yes?
Would you like to taste it?
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
Yeah!
The texture is good and it tastes good too!
Thank you very much!
Well then, until next time.
Farewell!
Yeah, see you later.
Be careful!
Is something wrong?
You seem kind of out of it.
Something you can't tell me?
I-It's a secret, okay?
Okay.
Actually—
Keiichirou, do you have a girlfriend?
Huh?
Chihiro-kun?
Are you all right?
I-I'm fine!
That idiot!
I told him to probe discreetly!
Why is he asking him straight out?!
Stupid!
Well?
Why are you asking out of the blue?
I wanted to know.
Come on, tell me.
Unfortunately, no.
Really?
Then, who's the girl in the picture?
Another direct question...
Picture?
Yeah.
I see.
So that's what this is about.
Gulp
Gulp.
Chihiro-kun, what's the matter?
Aren't you coming in?
I am...
I'm sorry for looking without permission.
Um, b-but it wasn't like I was trying to look!
I-I-It was an accident—
I know that.
It was my fault for forgetting it in the first place.
Well...
...which one did you see?
What?!
There are so many!
Huh?
The person in this picture is...
Yes.
That's Chiyo-sama.
Mom?!
Yes.
You really do take after her, Chihiro-kun.
Which means...
The girl in the picture is her friend or something?
What, what?
It's a picture of Nee-san?
Lemme see, lemme se—
Wh-Why is this...?
Huh?
Chihiro-kun.
This is a picture of Madoka-sama.
What?!
Well, you know how kids are.
Chiyo-sama had Madoka-sama wear her clothes as a joke.
He looked better in them than expected,
and Madoka-sama did not resist as much as usual.
So Chiyo-sama seemed to enjoy herself.
That's why... he even put on a wig?
Why do you carry those around with you?!
It is a basic rule to have dirt
on people that can be used when necessary.
You ingrate!
However, now that it's been found out,
it won't work as a trump card anymore.
I-I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I have other trump cards.
Wait, what "others"?!
Aw Keiichirou, don't you think
you have been especially mean lately?
I've been normal.
Keiichirou-san, what's this?
Oh...
That's Madoka-sama and Miyako-sama.
It was the first picture I took after borrowing a camera,
so it's a memento.
Oh, I see.
I'm glad.
Oh, is this me?
That's right.
You don't remember?
That's correct.
You were very young then.
In that case—
Let's take a picture to commemorate today.
Here, Keiichirou.
I'm taking the picture?
I don't know how to use it!
Please get a little closer.
Oh, okay!
That picture from earlier was
the first picture Keiichirou-san ever took.
He always carries it around with him in his planner.
I'm taking it!
Okay!
Okay, say cheese!
Chihiro!
I want more tea.
Okay, okay.
You have grown up, haven't you?
I'm already sixteen.
I won't be a child forever.
That's true.
Excuse me.
"What is he, her dad?"
Is what I'd like to say...
If you have known someone since they were that young...
Well, but...
Girls grow up and become beautiful in the blink of an eye.
He can become flustered then.
When that happens,
I'll point my finger at him and laugh,
"Ha-ha, that's what you get!"
Yeah.
I'll do that, too.
Chi-chan!
Huh?!
Why do you have them?!
I had Keiichirou-san reprint them for me.
Reprint?!
I thought they'd be good at keeping evil away.
Evil?!
Wait, are you talking about me?
That's too mean...!
Episode 4
What One Likes, One Will Do Well
Tadaaa!
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
Antaro? You're hungry, aren't you?
Here's some food!
Miyako-san, you can understand what Antaro's saying?
Yes! Antaro loves eating,
so he's usually barking "Feed me!"
That's all?
But yesterday he barked,
"Someone I don't know is here!" for the first time.
I was so moved!
I think that's normal...
Next time, "A Man Never Goes Back on His Word."
A Man Never Goes Back on His Word
He talked? Did he talk just now?
Please watch everyone, woof!