I hate taking out the trash.
Isn't there too big of a difference between cleaning duties?
Hallway duty is easy since there's no trash involved.
I like classroom duty the best, though.
There's cleaning the floor,
wiping the windows, and wiping the desks!
It's a full course!
For you, maybe.
Hey, don't run!
Haha, I can see your underwear!
Let's hurry up and finish so we can play dodge ball.
Why you!
Did we get a spot today?
K-Komiya!
Sensei!
A sprain?
Are you all right, Chihiro?
It's not a big deal.
It just hurts a little, but I can still walk.
You better not.
These things will swell up later.
Luckily it's the weekend, so please rest and heal up.
But what about meals and stuff—
That's right, Chi-chan!
You can leave things to me at times like this!
Madoka-sama, please don't get too excited.
That's mean!
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
For sprains, the most important things
are to rest and keep the swelling down.
(ansei)
(reikyaku)
(appaku)
(kyojou)
The term "RICE therapy" comes from the first letters of these words.
Icing should be done in approximately 20 minute intervals—
Keiichiro-san, more importantly...
I'm worried about the idiot behind you
who started to mop without sweeping first.
If we ignore him, he will tire of it eventually.
Don't give up! Scold him!
I've done it now...
It's time for dinner!
Why are they all sweets?
It is amazing, though...
Well, I tried to make dinner...
But after I thought about it,
I realized I only knew how to make sweets.
If you realized that, then don't start cooking!
How's the kitchen?
I... don't think you should look at it right now.
I knew it!
Jeez, I'll cook starting tomorrow.
It's not like it's a serious injury, anyway.
Nope.
If joint injuries don't heal properly,
they can have lasting effects.
But I have to clean as well.
Plus you only know how to make sweets!
Don't worry about that.
Tomorrow, we'll have backup.
Chihiro-kun, how are you feeling?
Miyako-san, you came?
Now we can eat meals that aren't sweet!
backup is here!
Please leave it to me!
Sharp!
backup is here!
Th-Thanks...
But I don't think I'll be able to help much.
That's all right.
If the backup needs help, that defeats the purpose.
Please rest well today.
Madoka-onii-sama says he will help as well.
Yup, yup.
Don't look so obviously uneasy!
Well then, I will borrow your kitchen.
Come on, Miyako!
Let's go do our best!
Yes, Madoka-nii-sama!
Oh, wait!
The kitchen is—
Madoka-nii-sama, a thief has been in this kitchen!
Oh, no, that's not it!
Will they be okay?
They're cleaning up.
Oh, Sensei!
I'm sorry, are you hungry?
Do you want a snack?
No, I'm fine.
We'll make lunch soon, all right?
Okay.
Huh?
Miyako's gotten a lot better, hasn't she?
It's good!
It's the result of everything I've learned from you, Sensei!
Good, good!
Chihiro-kun, what would you like to eat for dinner?
Huh? Uh... Anything...
Oh my, you're just like Madoka-nii-sama!
We often have Japanese food for dinner, right?
Y-Yeah.
Then, Japanese food.
Thank you for cooking.
Leave it to me!
Um...
Are you sure you don't need my help?
Yes!
Please do not worry and rest well.
Okay, thanks.
I'll help too!
As long as you do your best to not make a mess...
I'm shocked!
What's with this difference in treatment?
I'm so bored...
We didn't have that much homework this week,
and I was thinking of polishing the sink.
But they already cleaned it.
It's like it doesn't matter if I'm here or not.
If I'm not here to nag,
it's not like Madoka cares if things are messy.
And other people can cook, not just me.
It's like...
It's kind of... lonely...
Fire?!
Are you all right?!
I'm sorry...
It was fine that we decided on Japanese food for dinner...
But after I thought about it,
I realized my whole repertoire consists of Western dishes...
I thought just frying fish would be easy, but...
I'll clean this up right away!
I wonder if there's an easier recipe...
Japanese Hospitality:
Seasonal Japanese Food
What would you like to eat for dinner?
Alright then, Japanese food.
The two of them were trying so hard for my sake...
...and here I was sulking.
I'm an idiot.
I want to eat stew and dessert.
Miyako-san's cooking is delicious.
And I like Madoka's sweets, too.
I'll teach you how to make
Japanese food properly some other time.
Okay!
Then, what do you want for dessert?
Cake? Pudding?
Before that—
Yes, yes?
Clean up!
Very well!
Let's eat!
Japanese Hospitality:
Seasonal Japanese Food
Thanks.
Japanese Hospitality:
Seasonal Japanese Food
I'm off!
Have a nice day!
Watch out for cars.
Komiya!
Morning!
Morning.
Is your foot okay now?
Yeah, it's fine.
I'm glad.
Yeah.
What're you doing?
We're gonna be late!
R-Right!
Shounen Maid
Madoka, take care of yourself.
You space out a lot, so as your sister, I worry.
Make sure you tell me if you're getting bullied over there.
Don't worry. Keiichiro will be with me as well.
Bonjour... Merci... Au revoir...
Oh my, that's true.
Sorry, Nee-san.
You'll be all alone.
I'm worried about leaving you here...
You have got a pertinent mouth on you.
Stop that.
Your sister will be alright, because she's strong.
Go study hard and become an adult.
Then come back stronger.
It's a promise, okay?
Someday...
A dream, huh...?
Coming!
What's up?
I rented a movie I heard was good!
Your TV is big.
So I messaged Madoka-san to see if we could come over...
Sure! Grin.
...is what he said.
What, are you two friends or something?!
Thanks for having us over!
Welcome.
Let's start watching right away!
Ta-da!
Well... I-It's fine, isn't it?
It looks great! Like a B-movie.
Right?
Let's close the curtains and watch in the dark!
THE CURSE
Oh? Chihiro, you don't like scary stuff?
Th-There's no way I'm scared of this!
Really?
That's fine, then...
Wh-Who's there?
Oh dear...
That surprised me!
Why...? Why...?
No...!
I'm not scared, I'm not scared, I'm not scared!
Are you all right?
You don't have to force yourself.
I told you, I'm not scared!
Why...? Why...?
Why didn't you help me...?
I always... always...
S-Stay away... Stay away!
I can't take it anymore!
You're being too loud!
This stuff isn't real anyway.
There's no such thing as ghosts!
Yeah, you're right.
Well, that wasn't scary at all!
There's no scientific evidence for ghosts.
That's why I'm not scared at all.
Uh...
What you mean is... I can sleep with you today, right?
Hurry up and lie down!
Okay.
Now that I think about it,
Nee-san didn't like horror movies either.
Even so, if I asked her to watch, she always would.
Why?
How would I know, stupid?
If you knew she didn't like them, don't ask her to, stupid!
Not that I'm scared of them, though.
Huh?
Do you hear that?
Wh-What?
It's like something's... crying out...
I'm sure I heard that.
Is it outside?
I can't hear anything, stupid!
Don't say weird stuff, stupid!
Hurry and go to sleep, stupid!
What? But I can hear it. See?
Shut up, stupid!
Hurry up and go to sleep!
Help... Help me...
I was calling you this whole time...
Why... didn't you help me...?
Hey...
Why?!
Why...?
How am I supposed to know!?
A dream?
Last night I had a scary dream...
A woman covered in blood was chasing me!
That's just like the movie.
Now that you mention it,
there's a movie about a cursed videotape, right?
The one where whoever watches it is cursed to death.
Oh yeah, there is!
Have I been cursed?
Will she chase me until I die?
What?
Don't tell me you had a scary dream too, Komiya?
O-O-O-O-Of course not!
Rattled
He did, huh?
It's like something's... crying out...
That was just my imagination!
My imagination!
Th-That Madoka!
Why did he have to go out for work today?
He always comes when I don't want him to.
No, but it's not like I want him to come.
He's such a bother!
Have I been cursed?
Will she chase me until I die?
There's no such thing...
There's no such thing as ghosts!
There's no ghosts!
It's not scientific!
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
Getting
Angry
Instead
I'm only scared because I was thinking about scary stuff!
As long as I know it was just my imagination, that stuff is nothing.
No!
It's a thief!
Th-There's no such thing as ghosts.
It's just a thief, of cours—
SCREAM
Faint
Chi-chan, what's wrong?
I-It was a cat?
Anyway, don't come in from a weird place!
Well... I forgot my key to the front door.
On top of that, you're wearing misleading clothes...
Anyway, the real ghost is just this little guy.
I heard a voice crying out
since last night, so I'm glad I found it.
You're allergic to cats, aren't you?!
I'll take this!
So mean!
We get a lot of stray cats on the premises here.
It looks like people found out I take them in and do something about them.
Keiichiro's the one that actually
does something about them, though.
I just make him mad at me.
Then don't bring them home!
But it was calling out to me.
If someone calls out "Help me."
Doesn't it make you feel like you should?
Please adopt me
What about me?
Why did you help me?
Because I promised.
I promised my sister.
Someday, when I'm at the end of my rope,
come and help me, Madoka.
Promise?
That's why I kept waiting...
For her to call out to me...
She never did, though.
But you don't have to call out for me to come and save you, Chi-chan.
So don't worry.
What does that mean?
Even though our fingers are separated...
...the promise still remains.
What you gave up to protect...
I will properly protect.
Is that enough?
...Nee-san?
Huh? This dream again?
Help... help me...
If someone calls out "Help me."
Doesn't it make you feel like you should?
I-It's all right!
Madoka will help you!
He found you, so everything will be all right now!
What am I saying...?
Really?
I'm glad.
See? That's why I told you.
You didn't have to worry.
Now about what you should do. I think you'll be fine, so don't worry.
said...
Why do you have to keep bringing them in like that?!
Oh no, he's mad!
Of course I am!
But, but—
Don't "but" me!
Crying won't help!
You're lucky he found you.
Please don't!
Episode 5
A Man Never
Goes Back on His Word
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
Chi-chan, here's a cellphone strap for you!
Why is it so frilly?
It's the same design as your maid clothes.
Then it's obvious that it's yours, Chi-chan!
I definitely won't misplace my phone with this on it!
Wow, do you like it that much?
I'm so happy!
That's not it!
It's embarrassing, so I can't!
Next time, "Even Frilly Sleeves Can Be Good".
No, it's "Even a Chance Encounter is Preordained"!
Even a Chance Encounter is Preordained
Everyone, we're counting on your support!
Please watch!