"If you struggle when you are young,
it will be easier as an adult."
That's what my mom always said.
It was probably a distorted ﻿version of a proverb.
She gave this to me to give you ﻿if anything happened to her.
Dear Chihiro,
you must be surprised to
find yourself alone all of a sudden.
Sorry I couldn't stay with you forever.
I'm sad that I couldn't ﻿see you grow into an adult.
About what you should do now...
"...I think you'll be fine, so don't worry.
You're a worrywart,
so that's what I'm worried about.
Life usually works out okay somehow,
so you don't have to worry too much about it.
Do your best. Love, Mom."
That's too vague...
Calm down, Chihiro-kun!
You can stay here until you figure out where to go!
Those who do not work shall not eat
! !
But no matter how you look at it,
this trial is too much for an elementary schooler.
Anyway, Komiya, you sure it's okay ﻿for you to come to school?
Well, I took out the trash already,
and got things ready for dinner and to clean.
I didn't have anything else ﻿left to do but come to school.
You're such a housewife.
What are you going to do now?
Are you going to live with a relative?
I don't have any relatives...
Seriously?
Then, you're going to be homeless?
Do your best!
Yeah!
You guys are acting like
it's someone else's problem.
Please stand.
If you're really in trouble,
make sure you let me know.
School Route
See ya!
'Kay!
Honestly, the biggest problem ﻿is that it hasn't sunk in yet.
I mean, Mom was always working so she was never home.
It's kind of too late to feel lonely.
H-Hey, shoo! Shoo! Go away!
D-Don't come near me...!
Hey, you! Save me! Hurry!
Don't look at me like that!
It looks small and cute now,
but it'll get ﻿big and attack people in no time!
Excuse me!
It's true!
Let's go.
You were a big help. Thanks!
Hm? Huh?
Is your name Chihiro?
M-May I ask your name?
Was I right? Wow, you guys look so alike!
Nice to meet you. My name is Madoka Takatori.
I'm your uncle.
Huh?
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
I'm so glad, Chihiro-kun.
Now we can rest easy.
I'm so glad!
Welcome home, Madoka-sama.
I'm back, Keiichiro!
I brought him!
His boxes are outside,
so can you bring them in for him?
Yes, sir.
W-Wait a minute!
Um, I think you have the wrong person after all.
Did you confirm that it was him?
Of course! Anyway, you can tell ﻿by his face, can't you?
But—
But all this...
We were a lot poorer than this...
And she said we had no relatives...
Well, she was cut off from the main family,
so saying she had no relations ﻿is technically correct.
Could it be that she never told you?
The poor thing.
I can't believe she had heart failure.
The mother and child were working hard ﻿just the two of them until now, too...
Why...?
If she had family, why didn't they help her?
Because that's what she wanted.
Even if it disgraced our father,
she left home and had you.
She was free to choose ﻿to leave her parents' protection.
Then, I don't need it either.
I don't need help from you guys!
I'm going home!
Home? Where?
That place is not your home anymore.
I think it'd be easier if you ﻿just let yourself be helped.
You have that right.
Because you're a child.
Chihiro-kun!
What's the point of teasing him?
He was saying such cute things, ﻿I couldn't help myself.
He's exactly like Onee-san.
Does he get his strong will from Chiyo-sama?
His looks are from her, too.
Are you serious about taking him in?
I cannot imagine that you can look after a child.
I should at least be allowed to do this, right?
It was my big sister's one time being selfish.
The person in question rejected you, though.
It's fine, it's fine.
It's not like he went outside.
I'm sure he also understands ﻿that he can't survive on his own.
If I were an adult...
If I weren't a child...
Come on, Chihiro, cheer up!
If it weren't for me,
maybe Mom would still be alive...
Mom...
Speaking of which, where did he go?
Based on the direction he went, ﻿perhaps he's in the kitchen?
Ack!
The kitchen...? I don't think
I've been ﻿in there for about three months.
Wh-Wh-What the heck is this?
Chihiro-kun!
You better not think ﻿I'll allow this pile of trash!
Wow.
For some reason,
he's started ﻿single-mindedly washing the dishes...
That's why I've been telling you ﻿to hire a housekeeper for so long.
But I'm not good with strangers.
When was this from?
I won't allow it!
I just thought of something good.
Is it something pointless again?
That's mean!
You should believe in me more!
Please don't go overboard.
All right.
I finished!
Hey, look!
If you clean properly, ﻿it can be this...
This whole place is...
Oh, the cave of the sun goddess is open.
Good morning, Amaterasu!
My name's Chihiro.
I know that.
But I was just thinking that
I needed ﻿to do something about that kitchen.
It's so clean.
You should just hire a housekeeper or something.
And then have them clean your whole house.
Yeah, that's what I'll do.
I found someone good, too.
Oh yeah?
Comes with three meals a day and snacks!
A live-in position with a private room!
Covers school fees, too!
How about it?
Huh?
If you don't want to be ﻿indebted to the Takatori family,
then we can arrange for ﻿some give-and-take instead.
What do you say?
Those who do not work shall not eat
! !
Those who do not work shall not eat.
Those who do not work shall not eat
! !
W-Was that a prophecy?
Hm?
All right.
It's not like I want ﻿to live in a pile of trash.
It's a deal then.
I'm counting on you, Chihiro.
What is this?!
It's your uniform.
Why is it so frilly?!
You don't like frills? Isn't it cute?
Get out! Pervert!
What? Aren't all uniforms frilly?
I'm asking you why you think that!
Then, what about a different color?
There's yellow and pink, too.
I don't want either!
You're so stubborn, Chi-chan.
Who are you calling "Chi-chan"?! ﻿Don't act like we're buddies!
Shounen Maid
He's been cleaning ﻿without a break since last night?
Yeah.
Madoka-sama.
Why are you only bringing this up now?
What? But I did tell him earlier.
I said, "Why don't you get some rest?"
When I did...
How can I sleep in a dump like this?
Hmph
...is what he said disdainfully.
He was justified in saying that.
Why didn't you just have him ﻿sleep in this room first?
This is the only room that I clean.
I did.
But he said the corners were full of dust,
which was completely unacceptable,
and cleaned it himself.
Bam...
Bam
Kind of shocked
Kind of shocked.
Besides...
He looked really happy working,
so I didn't want to bother him.
I see...
By the way, ﻿why is he wearing a maid outfit?
Oh, that?
I made it myself!
I just gave it to him saying it was his uniform,
and he really wore it!
He's an earnest child, unfortunately.
Uncle's heart fluttered a little.
That's why I made a bunch of extras, too!
In other words,
you were playing ﻿around this whole time, right?
Was that a leading question?
Oh no...!
Please work. With your undivided attention.
Next is this room...
Every single room is dirty!
Damn it!
Why are there so many ﻿rooms in this place, anyway?!
You don't need them!
It's not like you're using them all!
I'm tired...
I want...
...to go home.
No, I can't try to escape from reality!
What happened?
Oh dear...
Please do not touch it with your hands!
I will clean it up right away.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'll pay for it...
No one said anything about that.
If you're tired, then you should take a break—
I'm not tired!
Aw, why are you being so stubborn?
I told you I'm fine! Leave me alone!
Chihiro-kun, you don't have to rush.
I understand that it's difficult
to settle down ﻿after being brought to a new home.
It really is dirty, too.
That's mean!
But you won't last long ﻿if you're always on guard.
You can relax more.
This is your home.
I'm... sorry...
No. My home...?
No... I don't know anything about this place.
Chihiro-kun?
He's sleeping soundly.
Yes.
I see.
Then Keiichiro, you help, too.
Huh?
If I had known this would happen,
I would've prepared something ahead of time.
It's hard to settle down without a nest, right?
Madoka-sama, what about this?
Oh, you can throw that away.
Oh, you're awake already? Are you okay?
What are you doing?
Setting up a room for you!
I was actually planning to have
you ﻿choose which room you wanted...
...but I figured you could just
change rooms later if you didn't like it.
It's my first time having my own room...
Now that we're done cleaning,
why don't we have tea?
That sounds good.
Cleaning?
Threaten
How can you call it cleaning
if you didn't even use a duster?
Threaten
Do it over.
Exhausted
Well, I guess that about does it.
Thank you very much!
INUZUKA FURNITURE
It's your bed, Chihiro!
It even has a canopy! Isn't it cool?
You can tell him if you don't like it.
Don't hold it in.
Anything's fine...
It's delicious!
Chi-chan, you're good at cooking, too.
Thank you for making food for me, as well.
There's seconds if you want more.
It's been so long since I had a home-cooked meal!
This is the best!
It's not something ﻿to be that happy about, is it?
But it's so good! It's the best!
My own room, huh?
Do you like it?
Don't come in without permission!
Aw, why not?
It's night time, so let's talk!
Discussing
our love lives
What do you want to talk about?
Discussing
our love lives
Our love lives?
Who'd do that, stupid?
Get out, stupid!
That's mean. You called me "stupid" twice!
Now, then.
What's he doing?
Chihiro, which do you like, pink or purple?
Green, I guess.
Green, huh?
For what?
H-Hey!
Do not worry.
He is always like this.
He seems kind of out of it,
and he didn't finish his food.
The play is drawing near.
But if he is ﻿focusing that hard, then I can relax.
The play?
Have you not heard yet?
Madoka-sama is a costume designer.
Huh?
He's always at home, ﻿so I thought he was a neet.
This room...
You can't clean here!
If you do, I won't be able to find anything!
It's the first time ﻿I've seen him actually working.
He's different from usual. Like he's an adult...
A late night snack.
Did you make all these?
Yeah, that's right.
What?
Let me borrow your head for a sec.
You're not going to sleep?
I'll sleep later.
If you don't sleep properly, you'll get sick.
You didn't eat much, either, did you?
Oh? What? Are you worried about me?
Gross!
I'll go to sleep after I get to a stopping point, so don't worry!
You're a worrywart. Don't worry.
If you pretend you're okay like that,
don't blame me if you work ﻿too hard and pass out.
Don't worry.
I'll keep my promises.
What does that mean?
It's a secret.
Life usually works out okay somehow,
so you don't have to worry too much about it.
I don't know if things will work out...
...but I'll do my best for now,
Mom!
Finished!
Finished? You're done with your work?
I'm finished! Look, look!
Look, look, meow! Cat pajamas!
I made the paw pads, too!
What about your work...?
I'll be done soon!
Don't mess around until you're done!
Episode 1
Those Who Do
Not Work Shall Not Eat
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
Good evening, everyone.
l am Madoka Takatori's personal secretary,
Keiichiro Shinozaki.
What's up? Who are you talking to?
I've known Madoka-sama since childhood,
so I know pretty much everything about him.
Like what?
He loves gathered frills.
That's true.
Shall I put frills on your shirts, too?
No, thank you.
Why not?
I feel like someone who looks good ﻿in frills will appear soon.
Don't tell me—
Next time, "Failure Is the Mother of Success."
Failure Is the Mother of Success
Be as frilly as you want.
Yay! Please watch!