Pink or blue...
Chi-chan, which do you think is better, pink or blue?
Yellow.
Yellow...
Yellow, huh...?
Yellow... yellow...?
What was that just now?
Oh, don't worry about it.
Looks like he's kinda busy right now.
You messed up in the middle of the calculations here.
Man, you're too used to this.
Sixth Grade
Arithmetic Practice Drills
What outfit is Madoka-san making right now?
Sixth Grade
Arithmetic Practice Drills
More idol clothes?
Sixth Grade
Arithmetic Practice Drills
No. Wedding dresses, he said.
Yellow...
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
Morning, Keiichirou-san!
Good morning.
Madoka seems to be busier than usual.
Yes, spring is like this every year.
This year, one problem came up after another...
I got fatter!
I got too skinny!
We moved the ceremony up!
Someone else's dress is the same color as mine!
It's worse than usual this year.
I see...
Oh, you're awake?
Want something to eat?
Yeah, I think I'll go with pink after all.
I see.
Maybe it'll be easier for him to eat if I make him a bento.
Sorry to cause you trouble, Chihiro-kun.
It's fine! I'm used to it already.
All right.
Chi-chan!
Thanks for the bento.
You can leave it there.
Do you still want dinner?
I just ate, so I probably don't need it.
Sorry.
Then I'll make you a midnight snack.
Eat that when you get hungry.
Okay, thanks!
Well he is eating... so it's fine, right?
Do your best.
Hello.
Um, hello...
Your hair's sticking up.
Huh? Who is she?
I feel like I've seen her before...
Madoka... Madoka!
Huh?
Oh, morning.
If you're going to sleep,
you should sleep in your bed!
But if I slept in bed, I'd fall asleep.
Then sleep!
It's already morning?
Hm?
You're a little hot.
Really? I feel all right, though.
But...
I'm fine, I'm fine!
Oh, thanks for the bento!
Now, let's do this!
You're not fine.
Smiley
Drugs
Chilly Sheets
Are these cooling sheets okay?
Should I buy some medicine, too?
But it doesn't seem like his head's hurting...
A Shot
of Energy!!
The Yun Series
Maybe a nutritional drink is better.
I wonder which one's good?
Oh Chihiro-kun, are you tired?
Huh?
Maybe I should make food that's easy to digest...
Like rice gruel or udon.
But they won't be good if they sit for too long...
I need to make sure he eats, at least.
It's my first time dealing with a fever...
Closing in...
Look.
Look at that. See? Look, look.
Disappointed...
Um...
Oh, Chihiro-kun.
Hello.
H-Hello...
You always see the strangest sides of me.
I just can't play it cool around you...
That cat ran away from you before, didn't it?
Yes, it's not a friendly cat.
You're on an errand today, too, Chihiro-kun?
Yes, Madoka has a fever.
Those two have never had a good relationship.
Oh. Is that child still that way?
I thought maybe he had gotten his act together a little.
When the seasons changed, he always got sick.
He causes trouble for you as well, doesn't he?
Huh...?
I'm fine.
Hm?
N-No, he's not always sick in bed like that.
He just happened to be especially busy...
Is that right?
The skies look like they will open up any minute.
Go on home before it starts raining.
Yes, ma'am.
Um...
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Chihiro-kun.
I couldn't ask her, could I?
"Do you not get along with Madoka?"
Or "How do you really feel about Mom?"
Or "What should I call you?"
Shounen Maid
Welcome back, Chihiro-kun.
Keiichirou-san, want some help?
No, this is the last of it.
It looks like it's about to rain,
so take an umbrella.
Here.
Thank you.
Sorry I'm in such a hurry.
Have a safe trip.
Keiichirou-san looks busy, too.
Huh?
Madoka, here.
Chi-chan, welcome back.
A letter?
Yeah.
Someone whose dress I made
sent me pictures from her wedding.
Oh?
That's pretty.
Chi-chan, have you ever seen a wedding?
Huh? No...
The real thing is even prettier.
It's like the whole thing
is backlit with a happy aura.
Huh...
I think it's the day girls can
be the prettiest they'll ever be.
That's why...
...the girls are really picky about everything.
S-Seems tough.
Yeah, well.
But it makes me want to make their wishes reality.
Thank you, Madoka-nii-sama!
Thanks, Madoka-chan!
Thank you very much!
Madoka, let me see your forehead.
Also, here.
Fever medicine.
If your fever gets too bad, take this. And...
A nutritional drink!
Huh?
I don't like depending on stuff like this,
but if you don't have an appetite, at least drink this.
There's gelatin and pudding in the fridge,
and if you want something hot, I'll make it.
You can talk cool, but it's no good if you get a fever!
It's fine to do your best at work,
but make sure you take care of yourself as well!
What do you say?
R-Right...
Even if I'm asleep, you can wake me up!
Okay...
All right!
Tender Loving Fare
I'll do my best.
Hey, wanna play video games at my house today?
Sorry, I have to go home.
Madoka-san is still busy?
Yeah.
Well, see you tomorrow!
'Kay.
Do your best!
Bye-bye!
Whoa!
Whoops, excuse me Chihiro-kun.
Is there still more stuff?
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Oh, that's a little heavy, so please be careful.
Oh, okay!
Keiichirou-san, your jacket! Your jacket!
Oh, thank you.
Have a safe trip!
Collapsed
Madoka! A-Are you all right?!
Chi-chan...
Praise me!
Are you done?!
Yup.
...as long as there's nothing else.
Yay!
And with that...
Don't sleep here!
Yep!
Madoka, dinner's ready...
Huh?
Madoka?
What's wrong?
Did you still have work left?
No.
This is Nee-san's.
Mom's?
Yeah, it's the first dress I ever made.
But I've remade it over and over,
so there's no trace of the original anymore.
It's now at around version 503...
Does that still count as the first dress you made, then?
I know she won't be able to wear it anymore...
But I always want to play around with it this time of year.
Mom said she didn't have a wedding ceremony.
Yeah.
There were no pictures of her either.
I see...
I'm sure Mom looked pretty in this.
Madoka, look!
You want to wear something like this, too?
Yeah, when I get married.
Then I'll make it for you!
Huh?!
A pretty one that'll look the best on you!
Really? I wonder if I'll be pretty too!
Like Mother...
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing...
By the way, Madoka...
Hm?
Here.
Save it for after your fever goes down!
You and your bad habits!
Huh?
Hm?
What's wrong?
Oh, uh, it just seems like kind of a waste.
What does?
That dress... for no one to ever wear it.
I'll give it to you when you get married, Chihiro.
Th-That's not until way in the future!
I wonder. It might be here before you know it.
I might not get married at all!
If that's the case, then you can wear it as a penalty.
Why?
Thanks for the food.
Now that you're done, go to sleep!
Okay, okay.
Where's the cooling sheet?
Huh? Maybe in my workroom?
Jeez...
Did something just hit the window?
Huh?
Aren't you just hearing things because you're feverish?
Hurry up and go to sleep!
Okay...
Night.
Cooling sheets... cooling sheets...
Aw jeez, he's so messy!
Where are they?
Huh?
Ah-ha! Those are the ones!
Thanks.
Huh?
That's just my imagination, right...?
Scream
What's the matter?
J-Just now, did you turn on the light?
Huh?
You heard that just now too, Chi-chan?
Could it be an... e-evil spirit?
An evil spirit?
The window's open.
No wonder it was cold.
Sorry Chi-chan, can you close it for me?
Chi-chan?
Hurry up and go to sleep!
Right...
Huh...?
An evil spirit!
Shh!
Let's let Madoka sleep.
What?
Huh?
This girl again...
I went through all the trouble of helping you,
and then you called me an evil spirit. How rude.
It's been exactly one year.
That's why I came to see you.
One year?
Hey, tell me something.
Huh?
Anything. What happened to you this past year?
I don't know who she is, but for
some reason, I feel like I know her...
Um... Madoka brought me to this house.
Yeah?
I met Keiichirou-san,
and Miyako-san ran away from home.
And... I practiced making rolled omelets.
I brought home Antaro, the dog.
I made pudding with Miyako-san.
I watched a scary movie with Hino and the others.
I met Ryuuji-san and the rest of Uchoten Boys.
And we had a birthday party for Madoka.
Madoka came to open house,
where I read an essay called "My Future Dream."
I did some major cleaning on New Year's Eve,
we went skating at the cottage.
We saw the first sunrise of the year.
I made macarons as thanks for Valentine chocolates...
Then Hino's sister Hana-chan
ran away from home and I cheered her up.
l made botamochi with Madoka and went to visit Mom's grave...
And...
I met Madoka's mom... from the main family.
Spring came, and we had a flower-viewing party.
Then I became a sixth-grader.
A lot of stuff happened, and some of it was rough.
But...
I wasn't lonely at all!
I see. That's good.
I'm relieved to hear that, Chihiro.
Oh, it looks like someone's here for me.
Hey, you — pull yourself together!
Mom!
Chihiro... See you later.
Mom!!
Ow... Chi-chan, did you flick me on
the forehead while I was sleeping?
Huh? My fever's gone down.
That might have been thanks to Mom!
Huh?
Yup.
It's perfect!
CHIHIRO'S SEAL
OF APPROVAL
Thank you!
Yes! Take that! And that! Yeah!
Oh Amahara, you're getting totally beat up.
Amahara, you suck!
Life usually works out okay somehow...
So you don't have to worry too much about it, okay?
No matter how I think about it,
we won't make it in time for delivery...
Schedule
Sparkle! Sparkle!
Crystal Tiara!
I'm the Black Rose Prince!
Justice is served!
Argh, you got me! Kaflump.
Where's the next enemy?!
Hey! You're slacking off again!
Keiichirou-san is crying, you know.
Jeez, you haven't improved at all this past year!
Don't make me tell you over and over!
Listen!
Those who do not work shall not eat!
That's mean, Chi-chan! I just got over being sick.
You were just playing super energetically right now, weren't you?
Don't complain!
Work like a horse!
Aw Chi-chan, you're too strict!
You're too loud!
Episode 12
All's Well That Ends Well
Ototachibana
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo