Japanese... plum?
Plums and peaches, peaches and... peaches?
That's a pickled plum!
Battle mode?
He was acting weird during breakfast today.
Who's he making clothes for this time?
Who knows? He did say there weren't
enough frills because they were for guys.
Frills...
Depressed...
It's a weird guy!
Don't avoid me and walk away!
Ow! Come on! I lost my wallet,
I don't have my cell phone, and I'm hungry!
You can at least give me directions!
Directions?
Do you know where Takatori-san lives?
Huh? You mean Takatori Madoka?
Huh?
I live at Takatori's...
Amazing! What the heck? This is amazing!
Is this fate? What are you, an angel?
Who are you?! Do you know Madoka?
Oh right, I'm—
Ryuji, from Uchoten Boys, right?
Oh, you could tell?
Jeez, I even disguised myself.
Who's that?
Thud!
Thud
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
Not Gonna
Say Thanks
Uchoten
That. Haven't you seen them on TV a lot recently?
I don't really watch TV.
There's the Uchoten Boys leader Hayato, Ibuki, and...
...Ryuji.
Nice to meet you!
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
Oh, what game is that?
Oh, I'm playing that, too!
Oh, really?
That certainly is Ryuji from Uchoten Boys.
Madoka-sama is currently working on outfits for them.
What? But why did he come here?
How should I know? You're the one who knows him.
I only met him through work.
Chi-chan, go and ask him.
Me?
I can't talk to strangers.
That looks delicious!
I can eat it?
You said you were hungry earlier, righ—
Thank you!
You're a great guy! A real angel!
Ba-dump
Delish!
There's none for me?
Ba-dump
So, what's with the fluttery clothes?
Are you a cosplayer or something?
It's my uniform!
Uniform?
Just so you know, I didn't choose to wear this.
Madoka's the one who made it.
Oh, Madoka-sensei made those clothes?
That's amazing!
Madoka-sensei is popular,
but he's famous for not taking on a lot of jobs.
It's super rare.
Oh?
That's why I thought he'd be more of a crusty old man,
so when I first met him, I was really nervous...
...but he's totally nice and really cool, right?!
He's the kind of adult I wanna be!
"A-Adult"?
That is!?
That is?
Oh yeah, this is no time to be eating!
Thanks for the food!
I came here to make a direct appeal to Madoka-sensei!
A direct appeal?
I... don't want to wear shorts anymore!
Huh?
Shorts! I don't know why,
but my clothes always look childish!
Why am I always the only one in shorts?! No more bare legs!
Can you guys even understand how I feel?
Even if I land a really cool turn, all I hear is "So cute!"
So cute
Sorry, I don't understand at all.
Huh? I can't.
Thud!
No...
There's no way?
I already submitted the design.
And they said I could play around with the details,
but I can't go so far as changing the silhouette.
Sorry.
I won't go home until you do it!
Even if you say that...
Damn it, I definitely won't wear those embarrassing shorts!
He hasn't even tried them on yet.
I thought at least Madoka-sensei would hear me out...
Depressed...
Where did you get that idea?
Well I'm short, so people always treat me like a kid.
Like patting me on the head when I greet them!
Can you believe it? I mean, I'm already sixteen!
I'm an adult!
I feel like it's not just because he's short...
But Madoka-sensei was different.
He didn't change how he acted like the other people.
That's why—
Sorry to bother you while you're dreaming,
but Madoka's tastes are closer to this.
Frills!
Frilly frills!
And shorts...
He tricked me!
What do you mean, he tricked you?!
You're the one who jumped to conclusions!
Y-You wouldn't understand!
What's with those frilly clothes you're wearing, anyway?
Even though you're a boy!
Don't make fun of me!
These are pretty easy to move in,
and they don't lose shape after they're washed!
They're amazing!
Oh, yeah? Then you can go out
in front of people like that, right?
It's not embarrassing, is it?
Of course not!
Sallying
Forth
I'm going shopping!
Sallying
Forth
You're an adult, so don't tease an elementary schooler.
It made him really depressed
when I first caught him in those clothes.
Oof.
Well, I'm going home.
What's with those frilly clothes you're wearing, anyway?
Even though you're a boy!
I said what I would have hated hearing the most...
I'll apologize when he gets back.
I'm home!
Um, sorry, I—
I got great deals!
Huh?
Everyone was like—
You're cute, so I'll give you a little extra.
Oh my Chihiro-chan, you can have 10% off.
All right, maybe I'll give it to you for free today!
They gave me a ton of extra stuff, and I got great deals!
This is great. Maybe I'll always go in this.
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
So resilient!
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Frozen
in
shock
Fight on, boy maid!
Even though I took it out on him...
What the heck?
I'm the one who ended up
being embarrassed by my tantrum.
I'm so uncool...
What happened here?
It's unusual to see Chihiro-kun go
shopping without changing out of those clothes.
Right?
Huh? He's your nephew?
Yeah. I ended up taking him in.
Head housekeeper.
But he didn't want to just be taken care of,
so now he's my head housekeeper.
Head housekeeper.
The kitchen is my castle!
Really...
Head housekeeper.
What did you think he was?
A-A secret love child, or something?
What?
There's no need to keep him secret. He's such a good boy.
I'm not embarrassed to bring him anywhere.
Madoka-sensei seems like a doting parent...
Unexpected...
Here, will you try this on?
S-Sure!
I knew it...
I think it looks good on you though.
Huh?
The shorts.
Because I look like a kid?
Because you have nice legs.
They're nice and muscular, so I don't think
they're anything to be embarrassed about.
I won't budge on the design.
After all, it's my job.
It's the same for you, isn't it?
Isn't it your job to show everyone what they want to see?
So cute! Ryuji!
Is that embarrassing for you?
Going home? You're not going to eat dinner?
Sorry, I left without saying anything,
so everyone's probably worried.
That's fine, but how will you get back?
You said you lost your wallet, right?
Did you
report it to
the police?
O-Oh no, let me borrow your phone!
Yes, who is it?
Ryuji.
Huh? You're from Uchoten Boys.
I'm Hayato.
It looks like Ryuji's been troubling you.
How did you know I was here?
Takatori-san's business card was next to the note you left at the agency.
Don't look for me.
I'm gonna become cool !
Ryuu
They found out?!
Ibuki's making something up to stall our manager right now,
so let's get back while we can.
Was Ibuki mad...?
Let's see...
I wonder if Ryuji thinks I act like a prince because I like it?
That's what he said.
He's really mad!
Uh, you—
Good evening.
I'm sorry our Ryuji caused you trouble.
Direct
Rays
Huh? You're from the same idol group?
Wha—?! I can do that too you know!
I can get super shiny!
Come on, let's go home!
R-Right.
Hey hey, can I come over again sometime?
S-Sure, but...
I'll wear the outfit Madoka-sensei made and do my best!
You'll watch us on TV, right?
Y-Yeah.
Oh my, Ryuji-san from Uchoten Boys?
I often see them on TV.
They'll be on a music program
soon so he told me to watch it.
I think it's on the Tuesday after next.
Tuesday after next?
It's the same day as his birthday!
Birthday?
Yes! What shall we do this year?
You're here too Chihiro,
so we should throw him a birthday party!
I know! Would you like to come over to my
house sometime to plan the birthday party?
Whose birthday are you talking about?
Shounen Maid
Oh now that you mention it, it's coming up, isn't it?
Madoka-sama's birthday.
So you knew after all, Keiichirou-san.
Yeah, I guess.
I didn't know...
That's because he's not really at the age
where he goes around telling everyone.
Really?
How do you usually celebrate?
We don't really celebrate it.
We just give him presents.
I see...
At any rate, he seems to think of it as a bother.
I see.
Yes, but I think he would be happy
if you did something to celebrate.
Y-You think so?
But I don't know what to give him...
Wouldn't anything be fine?
He would be happy even if you
gave him an empty tissue box.
I'll treasure this forever.
Wow, it's so rectangular!
He has so many clothes, so a necktie or watch?
He probably won't use them.
A vacuum cleaner!
Reading
carefully
Cyclone... paper pack... tight turns...
Reading
carefully
Wait, this is what I want!
I wonder what he would like?
I-Is this Miyako-san's house?
Chihiro-kun, thanks for waiting.
Hello!
Antaro, long time no see!
Well then, this way please.
Antarou
Th-This is amazing...
Oh?
Is this your house?
A nicer size.
There is a kitchen in the main building as well,
but this is my own personal kitchen.
Father had it built for me for my birthday last year.
A house for a birthday present...?!
Well, shall we begin?
R-Right.
This should be enough.
We can also make some chirashi sushi.
Oh, what about roast chicken?
It might be a lot of work though.
There's a big oven at home.
So if there's two of us, we can do it.
Okay!
I'm glad you're here, Chihiro-kun.
I would not have been able to make this much by myself.
I'm happy it looks like we can
have a proper celebration this year.
I-I see.
He accepts my presents every year...
...but we've never been able to have a party.
U-Um...
Yes?
What kind of present do you usually give him?
I bake him a homemade cake.
When I was young,
Madoka-nii-sama taught me how to make one.
Ever since then, it's become a tradition every year.
Is that right?
This year, my goal is to bake a large cake!
Chihiro-kun, have you decided on a present yet?
Not yet...
I don't know what to give him...
I think he will be happy with whatever he receives from you.
That's also what Keiichirou-san said.
It's just that I've been on the receiving end for so much— my room and a place to live...
So I'd like to give back at least a little...
I think those feelings would make Madoka-nii-sama happiest.
But...
Shall we take a break soon?
Yeah.
I'll make some tea Chihiro-kun, so please go play with Antaro.
There's a gazebo in the back garden where you can play.
Got it.
Chihiro-kun.
I'm sure your feelings will reach Madoka-nii-sama.
Don't worry.
Yeah.
Argh, we talked about pretty embarrassing things!
And after all that, I still don't know what to give him!
Shoo! Shoo!
Stop that. Do not come near me!
Shoo! Go over there.
This feels like déjà vu...
You over there! Save me!
Oh, you're a friend of Miyako's?
Yes.
I thought you were a very darling maid.
Who is she? Miyako-san's mom?
I came to get roses...
...but Kayako left to get scissors and hasn't returned.
Oh, Kayako is the lady of this house.
Guess not.
Then, is she a visitor?
Are roses in bloom right now?
They are.
Wow.
Are these roses?
They're "awayuki", which means "light snowfall".
Isn't their simplicity nice?
I was thinking of using them in an arrangement at home.
Really...
Oh, right! I could give him flowers—
Oh, are these for mom? Thanks!
Oh, are these for me? Thanks!
Never mind. Besides, he'd definitely let them wilt.
A birthday present?
Oh, is it for a cute girl?
No, it's for an annoying old man.
Oh my.
But I don't know what to get him.
Sorry, I'm troubling you with my own problems.
What is your name?
I'm Komiya Chihiro.
I see.
Chihiro-kun.
Does the present have to be a physical object?
Birthdays are days to celebrate someone's birth,
not days to buy people things, right?
That's true, but...
If you're worrying about it so much,
then he must be dear to you, right?
Think back carefully about what he
likes and what makes him happy.
Don't you actually know already?
What makes Madoka happy... and what...
Th-This is bad for my heart...
Ba-dump
I-I'm sorry.
My goodness.
If Miyako had to have a pet, she should have gotten a cat.
A cat?
That's it!
Thank you very much!
Madoka-nii-sama, happy birthday!
Huh? A-Am I in heaven?
It's your birthday.
It's... my birthday...?
You can cut loose today
without worrying I'll get mad at you.
Just for today, since we're celebrating.
Happy birthday.
Thanks!
Chihiro-kun, isn't it about time?
Yeah.
Here are the members of Uchoten Boys.
Madoka-sensei! Happy birthday!
Thank you for always making us wonderful clothes.
This song's for you.
When I told them about it,
they said they wanted to celebrate too.
Now, please listen to "I'm not gonna say 'Thanks'".
I'm not gonna say thanks.
Why would I spell it out
for you every time?
If there was something I wanted to tell you
It should be obvious what it is
Madoka-nii-sama!
I tried making a big one this year!
Wow, amazing!
Can we eat it all?
...for you every time?
I didn't know birthdays could be this great.
I wish every day could be my birthday.
Will you grow older every day?
It's fine, isn't it?
Chi-chan doesn't get mad at me either.
I'm so happy!
I won't get mad. Not until today's over.
Three more hours.
What!?
Are you going to save it all for tomorrow?
That's mean, Chi-chan!
Was it just a one-night dream...?
Oh well. It seems like he's enjoying it.
While I still can... While I still can...
It was all thanks to that person.
But who was she, anyway?
Episode 6
Even a Chance Encounter
is Preordained
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
Yoo-hoo! I'm Ryuji from Uchoten Boys!
I'm Hayato.
I'm Ibuki.
How did you like our song?
Wasn't it great?
I see, I see. Thanks!
What? Did you say Ryuji's legs were cute?
Isn't that great, Ryuji?
I-I guess.
That's all to make me look better, right? Thanks.
You're welcom—
Illustration
Hey wait, why did it turn out that way?!
Next time, "Learning Does Not Happen in a Day."
Learning Does Not Happen in a Day
We, Uchoten Boys, are also looking forward to it.
We're counting on you next week, too!