Sister...
You poor thing.
Being surrounded by strangers made you nervous, didn't?
I will go tell someone.
Please do.
Mother.
What are you doing?
He has a fever.
He needs to be taken to his room.
Keiichirou.
Y-Yes?
You know what to do, right?
Y-Yes.
Chiyo, you must return now.
But—
If you both disappear at the same time,
the guests will be worried.
Yes, ma'am.
Keiichirou, please take care of him.
Yes, Chiyo-sama.
What a terrible way to wake up.
Chi-chan...
I overslept...
To Madoka
Make sure you eat
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
"The fish swam smoothly back downstream.
'Clammbon laughed. Laughed.'
It suddenly brightened,
and golden rays of sunlight shone into the water."
Okay.
Next... Komiya-kun.
Komiya-kun!
R-Right! U-Um...
I'm sorry...
You won't move up to
sixth grade if you keep spacing out.
Then, please continue... Sakura-san.
Okay. "The net of light from the waves..."
Komiya!
Takei
Komiya
Amahara
Komiya?
Komiya
Amahara
Are you okay?
Komiya
Yeah...
The classroom has been cleaned, sir!
Please do the Komiya Check!
Good wor—
You have gotta be kidding me, Komiya!
I can't believe it!
S-Sorry...
Did something happen?
Your grandma?
The elderly lady I met at the park turned out to be my real grandma.
I didn't know anything until now.
So she was your grandma after all, huh?
You knew?
Well, I didn't know for sure,
but her face looks just like Madoka's.
I didn't notice...
Am I dense?
Um, well yeah...
But it's not something to be that depressed about, is it?
Thanks...
See ya...
'Kay...
Well, what was that about?
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb!
We're talking about Komiya-kun.
He's been acting weird for a while, hasn't he?
There are people who worry when Komiya-kun is down!
Do you get it?
You two are saying too much!
Oh...?
Hey! Are you listening?
You're his friend, aren't you?
Do something!
Hold on, time out.
What is it?
I'm busy right now.
Oh, Hinocchi?
Recording this afternoon got cancelled...
...so do you wanna hang out?
That's it! Nice timing!
Huh?
Well, um...
Basically...
I just need to cheer Komiya up, right?
Don't worry. Leave it to me!
Coming!
I bought a new game!
Wanna play?
Ryuuji-san?
Sorry, I have to clean the ventilation fan today.
Huh?
Huh
Oh, I'd play with you too, Madoka-sensei!
Let's play!
Maybe next time.
Shocked!
Shocked
What?!
Well?
They wouldn't even let you in?
Are you sure you're an idol?
But in the business,
I'm considered a healing-type, you know.
Hayato says it makes him feel
better when he ruffles my hair.
I was an idiot for expecting anything from you.
I'm switching to Plan B.
Plan B?
Coming!
Good evening.
Miyako-san?
You came out of the blue even though it's not Sunday, so...
Did you think I was running away from home again?
Well, yeah...
Um, Chihiro-kun!
It's almost spring break, right?
Do you want to go on another trip somewhere?
A trip?
Is there any place you'd like to go, Chihiro-kun?
Let's plan something together!
Sorry, I have a lot of homework today...
I see.
Sorry for keeping you.
Thank you for the tea.
No problem. Make yourself at home.
Chihiro-kun seems down...
You do too, Madoka-nii-sama.
Me?
Is there something worrying you?
If there's anything I can help with, please tell me!
I might not be able to help, though...
Thanks.
But... I'm fine.
And so, I couldn't get them to tell me anything.
Aw... you didn't work either?
I'm sorry I could not help...
Oh, don't worry, don't worry!
Nee-chan! The TV's too loud!
Who's that? Your girlfriend?
No, stupid!
Oh, sorry.
It's okay!
I'm worried because
Madoka-nii-sama also seemed depressed.
Why was Madoka-san depressed?
Perhaps he had a fight with Auntie Kazusa-sama.
They don't get along?
It's more like they are at odds with each other.
Oh?
It is a family matter,
so there is nothing I can do...
...but I wish to at least cheer them up.
What about having them relieve stress by letting loose and having fun?
I thought it would be nice to have a change
of pace, so I tried inviting them on a trip, but...
A change of pace, huh?
Wow, look at this!
Wow!
I said, you're too loud—!
Due to above average temperatures,
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Cherry blossoms already?
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
They're really early this year!
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
Sakura trees blossom a week earlier than last year
A week earlier than last year, five days earlier than average
~
the sakura will bloom a week earlier than last year
Cherry Trees Blooming
and will probably be at full bloom by next week.
That's it!
Nice, Onee-chan!
Huh?
Flower viewing?
Yes! There is a place where you
can see beautiful cherry blossoms.
It's gotten warmer as well.
Why don't we prepare some
bentos and invite everyone out?
That's fine...
But flower viewing can get crowded,
so I don't think Madoka will want to go.
Y-You're right.
Then, let's do it in the garden!
That way, Madoka-nii-sama can relax too.
That's fine...
But do we have any cherry trees...?
I'll bring a potted cherry tree over!
M-Miyako-san?
Gloom
I'm sorry to say that out of the blue...
It's fine, but what's the matter?
Gloom
Hino asked you to do it?
Yes.
Both you and Madoka-nii-sama looked down,
so we tried to think of something to cheer you up.
I'm sorry!
I-It's okay! I'm sorry to worry you.
But... well, I'm fine!
Maddka-nii-sama said the same thing.
Sorry.
No, it's all right! I'm sorry for butting in!
But please just remember this.
There are a lot of people around you who
are worried about you and Madoka-nii-sama.
Of course, I'm one of them.
Yeah, thanks.
Shounen Maid
Time to eat!
Okay!
Miyako went home already?
She said she would eat at home with her dad.
He would sulk if she didn't
spend time with him once in a while.
I see.
Thanks for the meal.
It looks good.
Madoka-nii-sama looked down...
It's full of spring veggies, huh?
Is he down?
Yum! It's delicious!
Hm? What is it?
Uh, nothing... Um...
Oh, right!
Miyako-san said she wanted to have
a flower viewing party at our house.
Do we have any cherry trees?
She said she would bring over a potted one.
Oh?
How about it?
If you want to do it, then it's fine.
'Kay.
That day...
What you are doing here?
...after all this time.
Now that I think about it,
Madoka talks about Mom a lot...
But I haven't heard him talk about my grandparents.
I don't know anything about Madoka.
Nee-san would make a bento for us.
Though the rolled omelets were a disaster.
But you know, I actually liked them.
I want to try talking to him about different things.
Miyako-chan
Re:Viewing Party
Thank you very much! I'll make a ton
of bentos!
Tomorrow will be sunny.
The day after tomorrow will also be sunny.
What's that? You got a message from a girl!
She's asking if you want to go flower viewing!
Don't snoop around in other people's phones!
Flower viewing? Sounds good!
You're not invited!
I borrowed one of Mother's pots.
The cherry blossoms are amazing!
Don't get so excited over everything.
Thank you for always taking care of Ryuuji.
It's nothing much, but please accept it.
Oh, thank you.
This is from me.
A bento? This much?
Yes! I was very eager!
I also brought these inari rice balls from my mom.
I brought snacks and drinks!
There's something for Antarou as well.
Oh my, thank you very much!
Is Madoka-nii-sama working?
Yeah.
I wonder if he plans on staying up there...
It should be fine.
I'm sure he'll come down when he gets hungry.
Then we must set aside his share!
Hey, let's get this party started already.
I'm hungry!
That's impolite, Ryuuji.
Then why don't we start first?
Yay!
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right!
Okay, stop!
Nii-chan, what are you doing?!
Hey, isn't it obvious?
The flower viewing can't start without the star!
Here we are!
Whaddaya think?
Now... please listen to the Uchoten Boys song,
I'm not gonna say 'Thanks'!
Yeah!
I'm not gonna say—
Hey, I'm the only one singing?!
Yeah, well you know.
I mean, we're not working right now.
What?
What, you're not gonna sing?
You can do it!
Boo!
You can do it.
You're a pro, so you'll finish what you started, right?
Yup, yup
I'm not gonna say "Thanks".
Kid, you suck at singing!
Why would I spell it out?
Maybe it's a little too lively...
Chihiro-kun.
I told Takatori-sama—
Your grandmother,
where your mother's grave is.
I apologize for doing it without asking.
Oh, I'm not angry about that.
It's just...
It was so sudden that I was surprised.
Madoka was angrier than me, though.
Yes.
Those two have never had a good relationship.
Because of Mom?
It's been that way for much longer—
Ever since Madoka-sama was a child.
I see.
Takatori-sama might seem cold on the outside,
but there is more to her than that.
Yeah.
I know.
You gave it a good try, kid!
Thanks everyone!
Sorry to interrupt the festivities...
But we have to get back to work soon.
Please excuse us.
What!?
Let's stay a little longer!
Later!
Bye!
What Hino-kun's like at school?
He likes to act grown up.
No way. Was that Uchoten?!
Welcome!
Hello.
Hey, Komiya-kun.
Just now, was that...?
You mean Madoka's visitors?
Not technically a lie
Um...
Those clothes...
It's cosplay! You know, cosplay!
Isn't it moving how hard he's working to make this party a success?
I-Is that right?
Y-Yeah!
Now, come in! Come in!
Thanks for having us!
Madoka, are you hungry?
There are lots of hors d'oeuvres,
so come down and eat some.
Miyako-san made a bunch of stuff, too.
And Hino's family brought a cherry tree, too.
It's pretty amazing.
And, there are rolled omelets...
I think the ones I made for today are pretty good.
It's like I'm the only one sulking.
I'll go down.
That's the cherry tree from Hino's house.
Oh, wow.
Madoka-nii-sama!
Now, come this way!
Please eat up!
R-Right.
Please drink up!
Huh?
Keiichirou, are you drunk?
How can you be sober at a flower viewing party?
It's just as dad says!
Yay!
You drunkards...
Madoka.
Here.
Try the rolled omelets I was telling you about earlier.
Let's see...
Thanks for the food!
How is it?
They're even more delicious than before!
Really?
They'd be perfect if they were just a little fluffier.
Fluffier, huh?
Okay.
Yes! A revolution!
Aw, man!
Nomura-san, do you want to play?
S-Sure.
But whoever loses has to do something funny.
I can't really drink sake...
Are you all right?
Thanks.
Sorry.
When we went to the grave...
I wasn't planning on having you meet that way.
Keiichirou-san said something like that, too.
It's not really anything to apologize about.
It isn't?
It isn't.
You know...
I always thought the people from the main family were cold.
I thought if I ever met them,
I'd give them a piece of my mind.
There was a lot I wanted to say...
But before I knew it,
I couldn't really remember what I wanted to say.
I thought they were so cruel, too...
Is that heartless?
Not at all.
I actually met her before that.
She felt like my real grandma...
Then she turned out to really be my grandma...
It was a lot of fun.
Really?
Well, I don't like her.
Everyone's getting ready to leave.
See ya!
It was fun!
Let's do this again next year.
Thanks for today!
Thank you for bringing the cherry tree!
Sorry my family crashed the party.
See ya!
Bye-bye!
Thanks for coming, everyone!
Thanks for everything.
Come back again sometime!
Okay! See you later!
Wait, where's Keiichirou-san?
He's resting on the sofa in the parlor.
I will also take my leave now.
Thanks, Miyako-san.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
Goodbye then.
It looks like everyone was worried...
You sure are loved, Chi-chan.
What're you talking about?
You were making everyone worried, too!
You share the blame!
Right...
That... dream again...
Even that woman...
...can grow old, huh?
Yu-Nii-chan! Chihiro!
Hana-chan!
Congrats on starting elementary school!
Thanks!
That new backpack is really nice.
I'm sure it'll get worn out real soon, though.
Sixth graders, please help the new students find their way.
Jeez, what a hassle.
Sixth graders are busy.
They have to be leaders in their clubs and stuff.
There's the school excursion, too!
Mom, I'm a sixth grader now.
I'll work hard with Madoka and
everyone else from here on out too.
So don't worry, Mom!
Komiya!
Hey!
What are you doing? Let's go!
Okay!
Episode 11
Boys, Be Ambitious
Chihiro
Madoka
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
Oh Chihiro, you're a sixth grader now, huh?
Wait, Mom?! Aren't you dead?
It's the preview, so don't worry about the details!
I can't do that!
More importantly,
t's finally time for the heartwarming last episode!
Is it really gonna end?
There's still lots of manga left!
All good things come to an end, Chihiro.
Closing in...
Life is short, and youth tends to throw you a curve ball.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Next time, Shounen Maid ends with
All's Well That Ends Well
"All's Well That Ends Well."
Please watch!