The boy maid, Komiya Chihiro,
is a fifth grader in elementary school.
Getting over his mother's death,
he works diligently every day to preserve
the peace and order of the Takatori house.
I'm counting on you, Chi-chan.
Are you just leaving it all to me?!
I'm Komiya Chihiro.
I'm working hard every day,
like my mom said to in the letter she left.
That's right. Those who don't work, don't eat!
Thanks, Chi-chan.
Grip
Madoka, you should be working too!
Shounen
Maid
Every time I start thinking words are a bother,
kotoba ga jama dato omou toki wa itsumo
I end up meeting your reprimanding gaze…
chuuibukaku kimi no me nozoite
When I come across a timid boy
kowagari no shounen mitsukedashite wa
I'll reach out and pull him in close
tsuredashite dakitometeageru kara
Even if the the hole in my heart can't be filled with the piece you find
mune ni aita ana chigau katachi no piisu demo
It's better than having nothing
nai yori warukunai
You just have to believe in what comes next
ato wa kimi ga shinjite
This is no coincidence
kore wa guuzen janai
Not quite yet, but it'll last forever
mada dayo eien ni sa
I’ll make sure you never lose anything again
kimi ni mou nanimo ushinawase wa shinai
With every innocent smile, I've come to realize
adokenai egao no tabi kidzuiteku
You made me a promise, boy
We're connected by our promise
tsunagou yakusoku
Episode 9
One Good Turn Deserves Another
Good
It's almost spring, huh?
It feels like I just met Madoka.
Hey, stop that.
Sh-Sh-Shoo! Shoo!
You over there! Save me!
Déjà vu again...
Oh my.
I-I'm sorry!
Oh dear, I wish people would be
careful when they take beasts out for walks.
Th-That's true...
Beware of beasts!
I guess dog-haters all say that...
Oh my, you have caught me behaving weirdly again, haven't you?
Oh, no...
Your name is Chihiro-kun, right?
You have saved me twice now.
Please let me treat you to a cup of tea in thanks.
Y-You don't need to thank me...
How regrettable.
Well, I suppose it would be no fun
to drink tea with an old woman like me.
O-Oh, that's not what I meant...
I'm just joking.
Um, we're not allowed to stop anywhere on our way home, that's why.
But we don't have school tomorrow...
Is that right?
Then...
Tea, huh?
Though...
...what should I do with all this?
It really must be crunch time with his work.
Coming!
Hana-chan?
You're alone?
Hino's not with you?
I hate Yu-nii-chan!
What?!
Hana's at your place?
City Pages
Anyway I'm heading over, so detain her for me!
Detain her?
Go ahead.
I'm sure you're hungry after all that walking.
It's yummy!
Really? I'm glad.
Yes!
Good job, Madoka!
Did you fight?
Puffed up
It was Yu-nii-chan's fault!
He invaded my privacy!
U-Um...
I won't go home until he is sorry for what he did.
So please don't tell anyone I'm here!
What?
Where's Hana?
Jeez, you have terrible timing!
What?
You're the one who contacted me.
I know, but right now—
Hana!
You can't come all the way out here by yourself!
Chihiro-kun, you traitor!
Hana-chan!
Hana!
Stop messing around!
I hate you, Yu-nii-chan!
I hate you! I hate you!
Hino!
Hana-chan!
Hana-chan?
Hey!
Madoka, I'm coming in.
What's up?
Did Hana come this way?
Hino's little sister.
I guess she's not here after all.
Sorry for interrupting!
Let me know if you see her.
He's gone.
It's no good.
Where could she be hiding?
Depressed
Sorry...
Are you okay?
What were you flighting about?
Friendship
Notebook
Hanako
Friendship
Notebook
Hanako
Friendship
Notebook
Hanako
A notebook? Hana-chan's?
It was just lying there in the living room.
And my curiosity got the best of me...
So you read it without asking, huh?
Shocked
Hey, Hana!
tHe littLe merrmaid
She can barely write.
There was no need for her to be that mad.
You got mad at your big sisters all the time right?
I mean, they were devils!
What's this? What's this?
An essay entitled, "My Family."
Stop it...!
Ooh, read it! Read it!
"I love everyone in my family."
I raised Hana carefully so that
she would not turn out like that!
Was there no going against heredity?
I think you're the one who couldn't go against it.
Anyway, we should find her and talk—
Madoka?
Hana...
She got tired and fell asleep.
Wait, she was here after all!
Well, when a girl comes to you crying and says—
Hide me.
—you have to hide her, as a gentleman.
You better not do that with strangers.
I said we'd take care of Hana-chan there today.
What?!
They said okay right away when I
said you'd take care of her, Chi-chan.
What, me?
They must really trust you.
Will you sleep over too, Hino-kun?
No, it's fine.
Sorry, Komiya.
Give this back for me.
Okay.
Did Yu-nii-chan go home?
Yeah, he said he would come get you tomorrow.
I see...
Do you want to go home after all?
I won't go home!
You're awake, Hana-chan?
I'll make you a dress, so come here.
A dress?!
Yay!
What kind do you like?
Um... Frilly ones!
Pastel
Crayons
Oh, we had fun.
Girls are great because they like frilly things.
You don't have to work?
You sound like Keiichirou...
Madoka-sama...
Man, I wanted to talk to her before she went to sleep.
Talk?
Well... I have to get them to make up.
It should be fine.
You only fight with the ones you love.
Huh? Then why did you keep her for the night?
I mean, she went through the
trouble of running away from home,
so I thought it'd be sad to force her to go home.
"Went through the trouble"?
Miyako ran away from home when
she was about that age too, you know.
What?!
I hate you, Father!
Shocked...
Shocked
It was far, so she came with a driver though.
Apparently he refused at first, so she tried to walk.
But she got lost, and the driver couldn't refuse her either.
So, I was always on Miyako's side...
...and Nee-san was always on uncle Otori's side.
Mom was?
Yeah.
She said "It'd be sad if we were both on the same side."
Your father's here for you.
Why don't you go home?
Don't wanna!
I hate him!
Super shocked!
Aw, when I saw how Hino-kun looked earlier when he went home,
Sorrow
I thought he looked like Miyako's dad
when he went home after Miyako refused him.
Don't laugh at them...
Jeez, isn't running away usually a more serious affair?
Hana-chan?
What is it? To the bathroom?
Um...
Wanna sleep with me?
Wow, it's like a king's bed!
It's so cool!
Thanks...
Oh, right.
Hanako
Ayumi
Here.
Hanako
Ayumi
Hino asked me to give it back to you.
Was Yu-nii-chan mad?
I don't think so.
Really?
Yeah.
If I had to say, I'd say he was crying.
I wasn't crying!
You know, I promised Ayu-chan.
It's a secret exchange diary,
so not even Yu-nii-chan is allowed to see it.
'Cause I promised Ayu-chan.
I think if he knew that, he wouldn't have looked.
Friendship
Notebook
Hanako
Ayumi
But then I said I hated him.
Wh-What will I do if he doesn't come get me?
D-Don't worry!
He'll definitely come!
Really?
Really.
So be sure to make up with him tomorrow, okay?
'Kay.
Shounen Maid
Ta-da!
Like a magical girl!
Yup, yup, you look cute!
Thanks, Madoka-chan!
Yay!
Jeez, you don't do your real work,
but you're fast when it comes to stuff like this.
Mornin'.
Morning.
Hana-chan, he's here for you!
What's with those clothes?
Huh?!
Is she still mad?
I don't think so...
Ta-da!
A magic wand!
Every magical girl needs one, right?
Now you can use magic!
Really?
Yup, really.
You'll be able to do the thing you want to do the most.
What... I want to do the most...
I'm sorry.
Me too, I'm sorry.
See ya!
I'm so tired...
It was a lot of work, huh?
You did too much without asking!
Hana-chan was crying, you know!
But then you comforted her, right?
Huh?
Wait, you didn't?
You should learn how to comfort girls properly.
Shall I teach you?
Angry.
Angry
Why are you mad?
Don't! Get! Carried! Away!
And then, and then, Madoka-chan—
Wow, look!
Oh, that's cute.
—made a lot of snacks and clothes for me!
He helped hide me, too.
Man, these clothes are too conspicuous!
And then, and then—
Am I being punished or something?
Schedule
Keiichirou, you seem quiet today...
After all I said, you didn't do anything
yesterday, even with a deadline coming up...
Schedule
Okay, I'll do my best...
It is not just your problem,
you're causing trouble for the client too...
Sorry, Keiichirou-san.
It was partly my fault this time too...
C-Coming!
I'm not gonna say "Thanks"
I got some time off, so I came to visit!
Why would I spell it out
Huh?
It's me, Ryuuji!
for you every time?
I bring energy to Uchoten Boys!
I'll shoot through your heart.
Well of course I know that,
but why do you have so much stuff?
Oh, this?
I'm sleeping over!
Where are you going?
Sleeping over?
What, you didn't hear?
Hinocchi and I made plans
to play video games together here!
Do that at Hino's house!
Sorry!
Crystal Tiara! Sweet Dreamer!
I got so distracted about Hana that I forgot to tell you.
Excellent Stun Grenade Launcher!
Oh, Hana? It's like nothing happened.
Justice is served!
Oh, cast some magic!
Magical Girl Hana-chan!
Ha, ha, ha! Rescue Mask is here!
Nii-chan, you watch this show too?!
That's so lame!
Rescue Mask-sama is handsome and rich, you know?
Sorry.
Oh, are you going somewhere?
Yeah.
Hino will be here soon, so you can keep playing.
Crunch
Time
Madoka's got a deadline coming up, so don't bother him.
There are snacks in the cupboard.
Don't use the stove or anything while I'm gone.
And don't open the door
for any salesmen or solicitors.
Don't play too much.
Take a break sometimes—
What are you, his mom?
Hey.
I'm going out for a bit.
Watch the house while I'm gone!
O-Okay...
Oh, is it already this late?
I'll be back!
Wait, where is he going?
Let's go.
Huh?
It'll be more interesting than a game, right?
A date?
No way.
Idiot, look at the signs.
He's going out even though
his friends are over and stuff.
It's gotta be a date.
I see it all the time.
Like from Ibuki.
Meat's ready!
Oh, I'm going to eat with Midoriko-san.
Sorry!
Shocked.
And then, I had to eat Korean BBQ by myself.
That's not him bullying you?
Sorry I'm late.
It's fine.
Waiting can also be fun.
A date
But she's an old lady!
A madam.
But don't you think she's pretty?
What? You'd even go for that?
Seriously?
Can I tell people about it?
Stop.
Um, thank you for the advice about the birthday present.
Oh my, I only chatted with you for a little bit.
You're the one who chose
the present and gave it to him, right?
Y-Yes.
But, um... thank you.
I wanted to thank you properly if I ever saw you again.
You're so conscientious.
Doesn't this make us stalkers?
W-We're spies!
For who?
So that kid's a madam killer, huh?
Stop thinking about that!
Ow!
Hey, idiot!
Is something the matter?
Oh, no.
I feel like I hear a familiar voice...
But it must be nice to be worried over a present.
I haven't thought about them at all lately.
Is that right?
But what about birthdays and Christmas?
My daughter and son both left home a while ago...
...and no matter what I give him,
my husband doesn't get very excited about anything.
Bored
But who is she?
She looks familiar...
Although, I do wish to give my
grandson various things if I could see him.
If you could see him?
Does he live far away?
Something like that.
It looks like he's doing well,
so I'm not worried about him.
But it can be a little lonely.
If you'd like, we can talk sometimes.
Oh, I'd love that.
But won't it bore you to hear
an old lady like me complain?
No, um...
I never knew my grandparents...
...and it's something I've always wanted to do, so I'd like it too.
Do you ever wish they were around?
Well, she was cut off from the main family,
so saying she had no relations is technically correct.
The poor thing...
I can't believe she had heart failure...
The mother and child were working
hard just the two of them until now, too...
Hey, let's go back.
Wait, why did you order so much?!
'Cause there's red bean paste in this!
Idiot, let's get out of here before we're found out!
Before you're found out?
What are you doing?
Mental Image
It's 'cause you were so loud.
What the heck?
You started it.
Aw man, we'll definitely be punished now.
Huh? What do you mean, punished?!
Um, sorry about that.
Don't worry about it.
You have interesting friends.
I will go pay, so go on ahead and play with them.
Okay.
Thanks for today.
Have tea again with me sometime.
Okay.
Thanks for the treat!
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm going with that man.
That's what I decided.
I'm sorry!
Chiyo gave birth to a good boy.
And Madoka seems to be the same as always.
Maybe it would be better if he came to live with us.
I'm done!
Good work.
I will deliver it now...
...so excuse me.
Thanks.
I'm so hungry...
Why do I have to do this?!
No slacking!
Punishment Time
You can eat after you finish sweeping all of it!
What?
Idiot!
If you keep slacking off,
we really won't get to eat!
I don't know what happened,
but why don't you forgive them?
No!
They really do look similar...
Could that old lady be...?
You over there!
Your hands stopped!
Oh?
Chi-chan, you went on a date?
I did not!
Oh? Who was it with? What's she like?
I said, I didn't!
She was—
I forgot to ask her name.
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
I miss you even if your past
I Miss You kimi no kako ga moshimo
belonged to someone else,
dareka no mono demo
this miraculous encounter
kisekiteki na deai wa
is ours alone
futari no mono da yo
Always looking back
furikaette bakari ja
leaves no room for new memories
omoide wa fuenai
Night and day I’ll become
Night and Day kimi no tame ni
stronger for your sake
boku ga tsuyokunaru kara
Love
I love you
aishiteru
I’m looking at only you…
kimi dake mitsumete…
It seems a waste to even blink
mabataki suru nomo oshii nosa
’cause you’re my entire world
kimi dake ga boku no sekai
I’ll always be by your side
itsudemo soba ni iru yo
Preview
Hello!
I'm Ryuuji from Uchoten Boys!
I'm Hino Yuuji.
Hey, Hinocchi, you sound tired.
It's just because you're always too hyper.
Thanks to you, this time was rough. Jeez.
We were caught 'cause you
were too loud, remember?
You're still saying that?
More importantly, what'd you think of me in a maid outfit?
It looked really good on me, didn't it?
I'm such a sinful man who looks good in anything.
Say what you want.
Next time, we'll bring you
"No Heat or Cold Lasts past the Equinox."
No Heat or Cold Lasts past the Equinox
Don't miss it!